
{\an8\fs32\fad(800,800)\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H666562&\b1}{\fn时尚中黑简体}翻译: 朽
{\c&HFFFFFF&\b1\3c&H666562&}{\an8\fs32\fad(800,800)}{\fn时尚中黑简体}校对: 史努比嘟 死不睡觉斯基
{\c&HFFFFFF&}{\an8\fs32\fad(800,800)\b1\3c&H666562&}{\fn时尚中黑简体}后期: 大块头要冷静
{\c&HFFFFFF&\an8}{\fs32\fad(800,800)\b1\3c&H666562&}{\fn时尚中黑简体\b1}压制: 凯撒
{\fs34}{\p1\c&H96955E&\fscx4200\fscy410\an8\fad(800,800)\pos(642,0)}m 0 0 b 0 0 0 0 0 0 b 0 0 0 0 0 0 b 0 4 0 9 0 13 b 4 13 9 13 13 13 b 13 9 13 4 13 0 {\p0}
{\pos(632,192)}{\fad(1000,0)}{\c&H00FEFEDB\t(0,2500,\c&H00D8D021)}瑞克与莫蒂
{\pos(617.333,622)}{\fad(500,0)}电波诚译
{\pos(617.333,666)}{\fad(500,0)}第一季 第三集
{\fn方正喵呜体}{\fs70\c&H20F0FF&\b1}电波字幕组 欢迎您的加入\N{\fs34}\N{\fs65\b0}官方网站:www.dbfansub.com\N{\fs34}\N{\fs65\b0}新浪微博:@电波字幕组
*最棒的圣诞 终于来到*
*Last king christmas last arrived*
*在圣诞这一天到来*
*On the christmas christmas*
我这火腿简直人间美味
Mmm. Jerry, you are really giving it to this ham.
圣诞快乐 嘿
Um, merry christmas. Hello?
我爸妈这么多年才来一次
My parents are coming over for the first time in years.
咱能把手里的玩意儿都收了 有点生气吗
Can we stow the gadgets and look alive?
在你爸妈面前表现的有点生气
Alive? For your parents?
呵呵 真好笑
Mm, good one.
你干嘛
Hey, man!
你干嘛
You"Hey, man!"
这个节日就是要有人情味儿
This holiday is about humanity.
是吗 我还以为是什么半神的生日之类的
You know, I thought it was about being born half-god or something.
不管怎样 所有电子设备都给我放进这个袜子里
Whatever. All electronic items are going in the stocking now.
爸 我才不会把手机给你
Dad, I'm not giving you my phone.
乖乖放进来 不然我就去注册Facebook
Put it in the stocking, summer, or I'm joining facebook.
嚯嚯嚯 大家好
A-ho, ho, ho, everybody.
我看是"啧啧啧"吧
More like "Whoa, whoa, whoa."
你这是搞啥 我爸妈马上要来了
What is this? My parents are coming!
淡定 Jerry
Calm down, Jerry.
这是Reuben 我一老朋友
This is Reuben, an old friend.
珍珠港
Pearl harbor.
我每年给他做一次医学诊断
I check in on him once a year and give him a little medical evaluation.
爸 真感人
Aww! Dad, that is so sweet!
呵呵 真感人 我不懂了
Yeah, it is. I don't get it.
韩国
Korea.
不用担心你的圣诞聚会 Jerry
Don't worry about your C-christmas, Jerry.
我跟Reuben去我的工作间
I'll be with Reuben in my workshop
你们就好好在著名的Phil Collins所谓"天堂"里过着吧
while you guys are having another day in Phil Collins' proverbial paradise.
{\an8\fs38}Phil Collins 《Another Day in Paradise》 讲述跟穷困的人们比起来我们过得就像天堂
真是不识庐山真面目
Huh. You think you know a guy.
我爸妈来啦
Okay, there's my parents.
别看电视 别玩手机 别碰电脑
Now, remember no tv, no phones, no laptops.
好好增进一下感情 就和传统的犹太人过周六一样
We are connecting this Christmas, like old-school Jews on a saturday.
{\an8\fs38}犹太教的安息日
嘿
Hey, hey!
圣诞快乐 儿子
Merry christmas, son.
嗨
Uh, hi.
你有事吗
Can I help you?
Jerry 这是Jacob
Jerry, this is Jacob.
你们没收到我们的短信吗
Didn't you get our text message?
没
No!
你就是Jerry吧
You must be Jerry.
这围裙很好看啊
That's a fine-looking apron.
威廉姆斯索诺玛的吗
Williams-sonoma?
{\an8\fs38}美国高端家居用品零售商
我倒想呢
I wish!
不过谢谢
But thank you.
你是我父母的朋友吗
So, you're a... friend of the family?
在我们眼中 他是家人
Uh, the way we see it, he's a part of the family.
哇
Wow.
你爸和癌症擦肩而过
After your father's brush with cancer
你叔叔也走了 所以我们决定重新审视我们过去的人生
and losing your uncle, we looked at life and wondered, how have we spent it,
和剩下的时光
And how do we spend the rest of it?
我们死的时候会是什么样的
What are we going to be when we die
是充满了恐惧和怀疑
a list of fears and questions
还是过了充实的一生
or a collection of real experiences?
天啊 Joyce 真了不起
Holy crap. Joyce, that's amazing.
然后Jacob出现了 我们开始重新享受生活
Then Jacob came into our lives, and... we're learning to live again.
我们三个一起
All three of us.
酷
Cool.
来点蛋奶酒吗
Eggnog?
这才像话嘛 这爷们有围裙还有蛋奶酒
Now we are talking! This man's got the apron and the eggnog, huh?
嗨 Joyce Leonard
Hi, Joyce. Leonard.
你好
Hello, there.
圣诞快乐
Merry christmas, man.
Morty 能过来一下吗
Morty, a moment of your time?
他快不行了 Morty
He's in bad shape, morty.
天啊 Rick 你干了啥
Aw, geez, Rick. What'd you do?
呵呵 Morty 你把我当成什么了
Gee, thanks, Morty. W-w-what kind of monster do you think I am?
我是在救他的命
I-I-I'm sitting here trying to save the guy's life.
我需要你帮忙
I need your help.
去找Xenon Bloom博士
I want you to find Dr. Xenon Bloom.
他知道是怎么回事
He'll know what's going on.
我去哪哪哪哪儿找Bloom博士啊
Uh, w-w-w-where where do I find dr. Bloom?
Reuben
In Reuben.
明尼苏达的Reuben吗
Reuben, Minne-minnesota?
桌子上的Reuben
Reuben on the table, morty.
我没时间让你刨根问底了
Look, I-I-I I don't have time for you to wrap your little walnut around everything.
结束之前屏住呼吸 不然你的肺就完了
Just hold your breath until the process is over or your lungs will collapse.
什么结
What proc...
爸 Morty呢
Hey, dad, where's Morty?
在忙
He's busy.
Morty 能听见吗
Morty, can you hear me?
往北走
Head north.
Rick我这是在哪儿
Rick, where am I?
按我注射的位置 你应该在入口的南边
Depending on my aim, you should be just south of the entrance.
啥入口
Entrance to what?
欢迎 Morty
Welcome, Morty.
欢迎来到人体公园
Welcome... ... to Anatomy park!
{\frz2.232\fs48\3c&H181B6D&\pos(648,254)}人体公园
{\pos(642,716)}这是我和Bloom博士一起搞的一个小副业
It's a little business venture I've been cooking up on the side with Dr. Bloom
人体内的主题公园
An amusement park inside a human body.
搞科学很费钱的 这玩意多多少少能补贴一点
Science isn't ch-cheap, morty. This should really help put a dent in the overhead.
天啊 太不可思议了
Oh, my god! This is insane!
脾山
Spleen mountain?
{\fs48\move(1256,102,532,102,9,3000)}脾山
膀胱瀑布
Bladder falls?
{\fs36\pos(824,250)}快来膀胱瀑布玩个痛快
{\frz347.7\pos(1070,542)}就在下腹乐园
胰之海盗
Pirates of the pancreas?
{\frz6.969\fs36\pos(960,384)}胰之海盗→\N就在腹腔乐园
你对最后一个有什么意见吗
You got a problem with that last one, Morty?
{\pos(672,718)}没有
Huh? No, no.
我只是看到什么就念出来而已
I'm just reading'em out loud in the order that I'm seeing'em.
好吧 我有点敏感
Okay. All right. If I sounded a little defensive,
因为胰之海盗是我的宝贝
It's because pirates of the pancreas was my baby.
我想建这个的时候遇到了不少阻力 Morty
You know, I got I got a lot of pushback when I pitched it, Morty.
我现在还是有点护短
I guess I'm still a little defensive.
总之快去找Bloom博士
Let's just find dr. Bloom, all right?
我在肝脏发现了求救信号
I-I'm picking up a distress signal in the liver, Morty.
去肝那儿
Proceed to the liver.
{\fs48\pos(576,556)}肺叶弹射
{\pos(1102,536)}结肠漂流
{\fs48\pos(834,526)}{\c&HB5FFE5&}鬼肝
{\frz22.52\pos(774,242)}脑皮层木马
{\c&HACF2EE&\fs48\pos(1072,292)\b1\4c&H4B3884&\frz352}膀胱瀑布{\b0}
{\frz8.326\pos(664,280)}前往 下腹乐园
前方到站 肝脏
Arriving at... ... liver.
小心站台间隙
Mind the gap.
{\frz6.8\fs36\move(142,554,1086,484,100,3200)\fad(100,500)}灰尘见谅
这儿好恐怖啊 Rick
It's really scary in here, Rick.
肝的情况不太好
The liver's under maintenance.
Reuben这几年过得很苦
Reuben's seen some rough years, Morty.
不要说三道四
Don't judge.
日子过得好的人是不会同意在自己体内修一座主题公园的
You don't agree to have a theme park built inside you if your life's going great.
{\fs62\pos(628,378)}鬼肝
Rick 有妖怪啊
Rick! It's a monster!
不 Morty
No, no, no. Morty.
这儿唯一的妖怪只有酗酗酗酒
The only monster here is alco...... holism.
那只是个机械狼人
That is an animatronic werewolf.
你是谁
Who are you?!
快说
Answer me!
哪儿来的
Where'd you come from?
我我我外公Rick让我来的
My my my grandpa Rick sent me!
Poncho 够了
Poncho! That's quite enough.
Morty 这是Poncho
Morty, that's Poncho.
这是Roger和Annie
This is Roger and Annie.
我是Xenon Bloom博士
And I am Dr. Xenon Bloom.
嗨 Bloom 我是Rick
Hey, Bloom, it's Rick.
到底出什么事儿了
What the hell's going on here?
我也不知道 整个安全系统都停止运作了
I don't know why, but the entire security system has shut down
似乎展品也逃出来了
and I'm afraid... the exhibits are unlocked.
展品
Exhibits?
年轻人 人体公园最吸引人的部分
Anatomy park's greatest attraction, young man,
不是音乐 食物 或者
isn't the music or the food or the...
胰之海盗
Pirates of the pancreas.
说话注意点
Watch it.
而是人体内最凶恶宏伟的病原体活体博物馆
It is, first and foremost, a living museum of humanity's most noble and ferocious diseases.
病原体
Diseases?
嘿 博士 最新消息
Hey, doc. I got news for you.
你的活体博物馆现在正式成为野生动物园了
Your living museum is officially a wild safari!
是甲肝病毒 快跑
Hepatitis A! Run!
东西要吃进嘴里去啊
Oh, the food goes in your mouth, girl.
噢 Jacob
Oh, Jacob.
不好意思 Jacob
I-I'm sorry, Jacob.
我还是不太明白 你和我父母
I-I guess I'm still confused about
到底具体是啥关系 怎么开始的
the precise nature and origin of your relationship with my parents.
你照顾他们的生活起居吗
Are you, like, uh are you, like, their caretaker? Is that what it is?
细节我们待会儿再说
We can go into detail later, son.
没什么可隐瞒的
Now, wait. Th-there's no point to secrecy.
无论生死都要坦诚
Let's all live and die honestly.
你妈妈和我共度了四十年人生 从身心到灵魂
Your mother and I have shared 40 years of each other, mind, body, and soul,
当心和灵魂永远相依
and when minds and souls are joined for eternity
而永恒的死亡在招手
and when eternity is At the door,
就该放身体自由
it's an invitation to let go of the body
去分享和尝试
and an opportunity to share and experiment.
爸 你到底在说什么
Dad, please. What are you saying?
不管说的是什么 听上去都很美好 Leonard 我们支持你
Whatever it is, it's beautiful, Leonard, and we support you.
你自己支持去吧
Hey, speak for yourself
爸 你这好像马上要说Jacob是你的情人一样
because it sounds like you're about to say jacob is your lover.
不不不
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Jacob是你妈妈的情人
Jacob is your mother's lover.
有时候我坐在椅子上看他们
I watch them sometimes from a chair
有时候在衣柜里 基本上都穿着超人服
and sometimes from a closet, almost always dressed as superman.
Jerry 这火腿是你的杰作吧
Jerry, this ham has got to be all you, right?
真是美味至极
It's incredible.
真有人情味儿啊 节日快乐 爸
Happy human holiday, dad.
肝炎病毒不会跟进呼吸系统里来的
Hepatitis won't follow us into the respiratory system.
{\pos(882,138)}肺泡林
奇怪
That's strange.
含气量下降了百分之二十
Airflow is down 20%.
那大脑肯定供氧不足
So, the brain isn't getting enough oxygen.
难怪安全系统停掉了
That's why security's offline.
我们最好去看看
Well, I guess we better check it out.
嘿 等等我
Hey! Wait for me!
戴上
Put that back on!
如果上到支气管那的过道去 就能找找是哪儿堵住了
If we got up to the bronchial catwalk, we could look for a blockage.
我去
I'll go.
别逞英雄 孩子
Don't be a hero, kid.
我没有
I'm not.
纯属找乐子
I'm doing it because it's fun.
我们不该在这儿
We shouldn't be here.
任何情况下都不要开枪
Whatever you do, do not fire that thing in here.
我们必须救下Reuben
We must save Reuben.
这是我毕生的心血
This is my life's work.
没事的
It's all right, my dear.
几乎所有人的肺里都会有这种细菌
Nearly all human lungs contain a strain of these bacteria, but
瘢痕组织能抑制它们的活动
The scar tissue keeps them... Dormant.
Morty 快下来
Morty, get down!
这些是什么
Oh, what are those things?
肺结核杆菌冲过来了
Tuberculosis coming in fast!
看我的子弹
Not faster than a bullet!
不 你知道你干了什么吗
No! Do you know what you've done?!
快去消化道
Get to the digestive tract!
他开始咳嗽了
He's coughing!
我不想死
Don't let me die!
深呼吸 Reuben
Just take a deep breath, Reuben.
你不会死的
You're not gonna die!
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
我叫 Alexand
My name is... Alexand
Rick Reunben得了肺结核
Rick R-r-reuben's got tuberculosis!
干得好 Morty
Oh, great work, Morty.
我这就治好他
Okay, I'll just cure it and then
好吧
Okay.
我治不好死人
Well, I can't cure death.
情况不妙 Morty
This is bad, morty.
你们被困在一死人的身体里了
You're trapped in a dead man.
如果情况继续恶化 对自己好点
Listen, if the situation keeps darkening, do yourself a favor
去胰之海盗玩玩
And pop by pirates of the pancreas.
很明显我不太客观 但我觉得真的超级棒
Obviously I'm biased, but I think it's great, morty.
一堆海盗围着胰腺跑啊跑
It's a bunch of pirates running around a pancreas.
我们也没刻意美化 Morty
We don't whitewash it, either, Morty.
那些海盗都特吓人
I mean, the pirates are really rapey.
第一要务当然是把你们救出来
The top priority is to get, you know, you guys out of there, but
如果实在是出不来了 一定要去玩玩啊
I'm just saying, if that becomes impossible, please, you gotta treat yourself.
天啊 什么东西这么难闻
Oh, man. W-w-w-what is that horrible smell?
熊猫快餐吗
You mean the panda express?
{\an8\fs38}美国中式快餐连锁
开玩笑 我开玩笑的
Kidding. I-I'm kidding.
尸体开始收缩并且产生气体了
The body is beginning to constrict and fill with gas.
我们在一具死尸里面啊
We're inside a corpse, my boy.
人体公园完蛋了
Anatomy park is doomed.
别管公园了 博士
Forget about the park, doctor!
我们怎么出去
How do we get out?
消化道就是疏散(排泄)通道
The digestive tract is the evacuation route.
笑点有懂吗
Get it?
结肠有一个应急站点 能把我们变回原来的大小
There's an emergency station in the colon with a ray that can enlarge us all.
我们去结肠
Everybody, head for the colon!
我还得听一个十二岁小孩儿的
Now I'm taking orders from a 12-year-old boy?
Morty 那些有结核杆菌的液泡是被人故意弄破的
Morty, the scar sacs containing the tuberculosis were sabotaged.
这件事绝对是内鬼干的
This disaster was an inside job.
盯着点Annie
Keep your eye on Annie.
她在西班牙油条摊的时候被经理记了几次过
She was written up several times by her manager at the churro stand.
进了肠道先往左 然后往右 再往左 以此类推
Intestines are ahead to the left, then to the right, then left, et cetera.
那啥 我其实十四了 所以 你懂的...
Hey, just so you know, i-I-I'm actually 14. So, you know...
啥
What?
不是十二
Not 12.
好吧
Okay.
因为他刚才说我十二
You know, because he just said I was 12.
哦 挺好的
Oh. Good for you.
啊哦 出师不利啊 Morty
Oof. Ugh. Morty. Strike one.
*奇妙之路呀食物之旅*
*It's a road of wonder, a trail of food*
*是好是坏都消化干净*
*It's a pathway to break up the bad and good*
*吸收剩下的全排出去*
*It's a tube that digests and then sends out the rest*
*小小的小肠呀*
*It's a small, small intestine*
这还得走好一阵呢
It goes on like this for miles.
然后就到大肠啦
Then we get to the large intestine!
嘘 有动静
Shh! I hear something.
别动
Don't move.
只要我们不动 淋球菌是看不见我们的
Gonorrhea can't see us if we don't move.
哦不对 记成霸王龙了
Wait, I was wrong. I was thinking of a T. Rex.
快跑
Move!
我们现在就是活靶子啊
We're sitting ducks!
博士 现在尸体里开始产生气体了是吗
Doc, didn't you say that the body was filling with gas?
是的 怎么了
Yes. Why?
孩子 你真是个天才
Kid, you're a genius.
你疯啦
Are you mad?!
都躲到这儿来
Everybody, in here!
嘿 淋球菌 尝尝灼痛(淋病症状之一)的感觉吧
Hey, gonorrhea! How's this for a burning sensation?
*鼓手敲啊敲*
*Drummer drum drum*
*敲啊敲啊敲*
*drum drum drum drum drum drum drum drum drum*
*圣诞小鼓*
*Christmas drums*
唱啊 Summer
Oh, sing it, Summer
*圣诞小鼓*
*Christmas drums*
- *小哥在敲*  - 我真喜欢听你唱歌
- *Being played by a bo-o-o-y* - oh I love to hear you sing.
Jerry 别这样 你不就想要这样吗
Jerry, come on. This is what you wanted.
我懂的 Beth 愿不能乱许
I get it, Beth. Be careful what you wish for.
拿了你的iPad我遭报应了
I'm being punished for taking your iPad.
Jerry 别多想了
What? Jerry, let that stuff go, okay?
之前是我不对
I'm sorry I was a bitch earlier.
享受当下吧
Let's just be here.
- Summer  - Ethan
- Summer! - Ethan?
你来干嘛
What are you doing here?
这几个小时我一直在给你发短信
I've been texting you for hours!
你在搞什么鬼
What the hell?!
手机不在我身上 我在过有人情味儿的节日呢
I don't have my phone! I'm doing a human holiday!
你有考虑过我的感受吗
Well, did you even consider how that might make me feel?!
你的感受
How you feel?!
什么事儿都非得和你扯上关系吗
Why is everything always happening to you?!
Summer 你有男朋友
Summer, do you have a boyfriend?
是啊 Summer 你有吗
Yeah, do you, Summer?
我不知道啊 Ethan 我有吗
I don't know, Ethan. Do I?!
Jerry 无意冒犯 但是你真得和家人好好增进下感情啊
Jerry, no disrespect, but you really need to connect more with your family, man.
我应该能用备用电源启动放大射线
I should be able to access the backup generator to get the growth ray online.
如果行得通 几分钟内我们就能回到正常大小了
If it works, we'll be regular-sized in a few minutes.
但愿Reuben现在不是躺在白地毯或者垫子上啥的
I just hope Reuben's not in a room with white carpets or upholstery.
这是什么东西
What the hell is that?
括约肌大坝
The sphincter dam.
Reuben开始大小便失禁以后我们修的
We built it when Reuben became incontinent,
但他死了以后就承受不住了
but it was not designed to hold a corpse load.
马上就好了
I've almost got it.
大家都站到圈里去
Everybody, move inside the circle.
Poncho 你包里这是什么
Poncho? What is this in your backpack?
那是黑死病病毒
That's bubonic plague!
你带着这个做什么 Poncho
What are you doing with that, Poncho?
都给我退后
Everybody, get back!
Poncho 你这个混蛋
Poncho, you son of a bitch!
你把结核菌放了出来 好从我这儿偷东西
You released the tuberculosis so you could steal from me?
说的没错
That's right, baby.
一大票人愿意为了削减人口出大价钱
A lot of people would pay top dollar to decimate the population.
我直接卖给出价最高的人
I'll take the highest bidder
基地组织 朝鲜 共和党人 圣地兄弟会
Al-qaeda, north korea, republicans, shriners,
健身的秃子
balding men that work out,
看日本少年动画才能性奋的死宅
people on the internet that are only turned on by cartoons of japanese teenagers
怎么都比给你干活强
anything is better than working for you,
你这个自命不凡 疏忽大意
you pompous, negligent,
节日津贴就给发iTunes礼品卡的傻...
iTunes-gift-card-as-a-holiday-bonus-giving mother...
得了吧
Come on!
滚开
Get off!
看啊
You guys!
要炸了 快跑
It's gonna burst! Go! Go, go, go!
我的脚卡住了
My foot is stuck.
不
No!
没事的 你们走
It's okay! It's okay. Just go.
告诉我的家人我爱他们
Tell my family I love them.
他们不太好找 因为我老婆留着娘家姓
They may be hard to find'cause my wife kept her last name
孩子也随她姓
and she made the kids take it, too,
我也没啥法子 不然你们...
So, I-I don't know, you can
不
No!
我问你一个问题 Ethan
Let me ask you a question, Ethan.
你的愤怒从何而来
Where's the anger coming from, man?
Summer是个贱人
From Summer being a total bitch!
你到底在气什么
Where's the anger coming from?
我哥哥 有一次带我去钓鱼 然后在树丛里
My brother... took me fishing once... in the bushes...
不行 我不行
I can't... I can't...
他像对女孩子那样
He made me feel like a girl!
他让我成了一个女孩
I...he made me a girl!
他没有改变你
He didn't make you anything, man.
你就是你
You are who you are.
她就是她
She is who she is.
去她那里吧 带着崭新的自己
Now, you go to her... brand-new.
过来
Come here, right now.
天啊 我很抱歉 Ethan
Oh, my god. I'm so sorry, Ethan!
我爱你
I love you!
我也很爱你
I love you so much.
你又做到了 亲爱的
You did it again, cubbie.
来
Come here.
停下 我讨厌这样
No! Stop! I hate this!
圣诞节可不在乎你讨厌什么 儿子
Well, Christmas doesn't revolve around what you hate, son.
那我讨厌圣诞节
Well, then I hate Christmas!
去你的人情味儿 你们真是又逊又恶心
Enjoy being human! You guys are gross and lame.
我叫Reuben Ridley
My name's Reuben Ridley.
你们现在在我的身体里
You're inside me right now, but
但在这趟旅途结束时
By the end of this journey...
我会在你们所有人心里
I'll be inside all of you.
我的故事始于九十年代互联网泡沫破裂时期
My story begins during the dot-com crash in the early '90s.
你想把手指伸到哪里都可以哦
You can put your fingers wherever you want.
Morty 你能调成静音吗
Morty, you want to put it on mute or something?
我需要集中注意力
I'm I'm trying to concentrate.
呃 Rick
Uh... Rick?
别吵 Jerry
Not now, Jerry.
我有件很"小"的"小"事要处理
I've got much, much smaller fish to fry.
如果我之前说了你什么 我很抱歉
I wanted to say I'm sorry I ever judged you.
你现在是我最正常的亲戚了
Right now, you're my sanest relative.
亲戚(相对)
Relative.
相对尺寸
R-relative size!
Jerry 递一把手术刀和一捆炸药给我
Jerry, hand me a scalpel and a bundle of dynamite.
Morty 你能去左乳头吗
Morty, can you get to the left nipple?
你开玩笑吗 我还想两边都玩呢 Rick
Are you kidding? I'm hoping I can get to both of 'em, Rick.
不 Morty 我说的是Reuben的左乳头
No, Morty, I'm talking about Reuben's left nipple.
我们得去左乳头
We need to get to the left nipple!
尸体开始腐烂了
The body is decaying.
动脉运输系统已经没用了
The arterial transit system is useless.
我们可以试试列车
We can try the service shuttle.
是连在骨骼系统上的
It's connected to the skeletal system.
所以叫做骨头列车
That's why we call it the bone train.
小姐 你愿意乘坐骨头列车吗
Would you like to ride the bone train, miss?
如果能让我们出去
If it'll get us out of here.
你呢 Morty
How about you, Morty?
你愿意搭乘骨头列车吗
Would you like to ride the bone train?
别磨叽了
Why are you doing this bit?
我们都要死了 快走
We're gonna die! Let's go!
看来你挺忙的
Well... I can see you're busy.
圣诞快乐 Rick
Merry christmas, Rick.
没有自动驾驶装置
There's no autopilot.
得有个人留在这儿手动操作
One of us will have to stay here and operate it manually.
呃
Uh, well...
不 你是对的
No, you're you're right.
我真是个混蛋 竟然还犹豫
I-it was a dick move for me to even pause like that.
这都是我的错
This is all my fault.
你们上去吧
You go on.
那是什么鬼东西
What the hell is that?
大肠杆菌爆发
E. Coli outbreak.
快上去
Hurry!
等等 有自动驾驶装置啊
Wait, there is an autopilot.
等等
Wait!
算了 没事了
It's okay! Never mind!
反正我本来就打算牺牲的
I wanted to sacrifice myself anyway!
它们把门弄破了
They're they're chewing through the doors!
我们到乳晕了 Rick 马上就到乳头
We're in the areola, Rick, almost to the nipple,
但现在情况不是很乐观
But we're also in a really bad situation!
马上就好 Morty
I'm almost there, Morty!
全国各地发来报道
Reports from all over the country have been coming in
一个巨大裸男出现在美国大陆上空
About what appears to be a giant, naked man over the continental united states.
我们现在联线纽约的Tom Randolph Tom你好
We now go to Tom Randolph in New York.Tom?
他的眼睛既不闪烁 他的酒窝也没有欢乐
Well, the eyes aren't twinkling and the dimples aren't merry,
不过我头上这鼻子确实像个七十英里长的樱桃
but I'm standing under a nose like a 70-mile cherry.
{\an8\fs38}出自诗歌《A Visit from St. Nicholas》\N"他的眼睛闪闪发光 他的酒窝充满欢乐 他的面颊如玫瑰 他的鼻子像樱桃"
谢谢 Tom
Thank you, Tom.
我们现在联线洛杉矶的Eric McMahan
Let's go now to Eric McMahan in Los Angeles.
西海岸这边是巨大的脚 Bill
We've got feet here on the west coast, Bill,
对于这种尺寸的巨人来说也是很大的脚了
giant feet, even relative to the giant man's size
至于巨人是有多"大" 就不必我多说了
, and you know what they say about that.
如果老话说的没错
Well, if the old adage is true,
{\an8\fs38}西方民间说法 脚大的人下面也大
洛基山那儿的"下面"就简直不敢想象了
one can only wonder what's going down in the rocky mountains.
啥
Wha..?
天啊 轨道
Oh my god, the track!
是甲肝病毒
It's hepatitis A!
乳腺孔
The nipple hole.
好美
It's beautiful.
哦不
Oh, no!
- 哇  - 是丙肝病毒
- Whoa! - It's hepatitis C!
我们认识他吗
Um... wait, did we have some sort of relationship with him?
可能他们人就这样吧
I think they're just like that?
就是人好
I think they're just good guys.
Bloom博士呢
Where's dr. Bloom?
抱歉 Rick 他死了
I'm sorry, Rick, but he's dead.
该死 Morty 我就要求你这么一件事
God damn it, Morty. I ask you to do one thing!
Jerry都不知道他错过了什么
Jerry doesn't know what he's missing.
他会想通的 Beth
He'll come around, Beth.
圣诞是个特殊的日子
Christmas is a special time.
能以意想不到的方式使家人欢聚
It has funny ways of bringing families together.
我不知道 Jacob
I don't know, Jacob.
Jerry今天本可以有点生气的 但他拒绝了
Jerry got an invitation to be alive today, and he rejected it.
我不知道我们的婚姻是否还能...
I don't know if our marriage will...
下血雨了
It's raining blood!
该死 去找Jerry
Oh, shit. Find Jerry.
Jerry
Jerry!
没事的 电视上说不用担心
It's all right. The TV says there's nothing to worry about.
巨大的浮空圣诞老人爆炸了
The giant, naked sky santa has exploded.
血和脏器碎块正飘零而下
Blood and chunks of viscera are raining down on the country.
不过应该没什么问题
Everything should be fine.
太好了
Oh, yes.
爸 能把手机还给我吗
Dad, can I have my phone back?
当然可以 给
Sure, sweetie. Here.
大家都拿件电子产品吧
Everybody, take a device.
帮助放松身心
It'll help you relax.
真好
This is nice.
是啊
Yeah.
我想这个圣诞我们都学到了什么 Jacob
Look, I guess we really learned something this christmas, Jacob.
爸 没这回事
No, we didn't, dad.
没这回事
No, we didn't.
Bloom博士真是可惜
Too bad about Dr. Bloom.
他是个天才 只有他能再造一个人体公园
He was a genius, the only man capable of creating a new anatomy park.
其实 我研究过Bloom博士的成果
Actually, I studied Dr. Bloom's work.
我觉得我能再造出一个全新的 也更安全的公园
I-I-I-I believe I have the knowledge necessary to create an entirely new, much safer park.
那胰之海盗呢
What about... Pirates of the pancreas?
我觉得那被严重低估了
I think it was one of the most underrated attractions.
好极了 屏住呼吸
Boo-yah! Hold your breath.
你干嘛 Rick
Hey, w-w-what the hell, Rick?!
搞什么啊 我喜欢她
What the hell, man! I liked her!
进展很不错啊 Rick
I really had something going there, Rick!
我都听到了
Yeah, so I heard.
你躲过了一劫 Morty 相信我
You dodged a bullet, Morty, trust me.
她下面可肿了
Puffy vagina.
这有什么
W-what's wrong with that?
我不觉得这有什么问题啊
That doesn't sound like a problem to me.
好吧 我不知道
I don't know.
走 去找点吃的 我要饿死了
Come on, let's get some stuffing. I'm starving.
真是难以置信
Oh, unbelievable.
一群机器人 电脑族
We got we got a bunch of robot, computer people,
坐在这儿 脸死命凑在屏幕上
sitting around with their faces stuffed into computer screens.
你们知道今天是基督的生日吗
Do you guys realize that Christ was born today?
耶稣基督 救世主 是在今天出生的
Jesus christ, our savior, was born today.
你们还是人吗
Are are are you people even human?
这算是什么圣诞
What kind of christmas is this?
嘿 Rick
Hey, rick?
Rick 能听见吗
Rick, can you hear me?
非常清楚 Annie
Loud and clear, Annie.
很好
Great.
在这儿的还有Alejandro 首席构想官
We're also on with Alejandro, our chief imaginarian.
嗨 Rick
Hey, Rick.
显微市场部的Natalie Jacobs和Chris Deseter
Natalie Jacobs and Chris Deseter from microscopic marketing,
器官概念部的Zack 以及新媒体部的Jamie
Zack from organ concepts, and Jamie from new media.
大家好
Hey, everybody.
那么 胰之海盗
So, pirates of the pancreas.
没错 说吧
Yeah. Talk to me.
嗨 Rick 我是Alejandro
Hey, Rick. It's Alejandro speaking.
我们认真的反思了一下
Um, so, we asked ourselves, internally we asked ourselves over here,
"胰 是做什么的"
"Okay, what does a pancreas do?"
结论是"它产生海盗"吗
And the answer was, "Does it make pirates?"
不 它产生的是胰岛素
No, it makes insulin, you know?
所以我们打算开展一个新的...
So, we're starting with a new...
那些人在我体内 是吗 在建公园啥的
Those guys are inside me, huh? Like, building a park?
那些人在你体内建垃圾 Ethan
Those guys are inside you building a piece of shit, Ethan!
他们建的是妥协让步的丰碑
They're inside you building a monument to compromise!
[哔]这群人 [哔]这整件事 Ehtan
Those people. This whole thing, Ethan.
酷啊
Cool.
那么 谁付我钱啊
And who pays me?

