
{\an8\fs32\fad(800,800)\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H666562&\b1}{\fn时尚中黑简体}翻译: 大岛优子一生推  Gaby
{\c&HFFFFFF&\b1\3c&H666562&}{\an8\fs32\fad(800,800)}{\fn时尚中黑简体}校对: 史努比史酷比
{\c&HFFFFFF&}{\an8\fs32\fad(800,800)\b1\3c&H666562&}{\fn时尚中黑简体}后期: 小萌
{\c&HFFFFFF&\an8}{\fs32\fad(800,800)\b1\3c&H666562&}{\fn时尚中黑简体\b1}压制: 凯撒
{\fs34}{\p1\c&H96955E&\fscx4200\fscy410\an8\fad(800,800)\pos(642,0)}m 0 0 b 0 0 0 0 0 0 b 0 0 0 0 0 0 b 0 4 0 9 0 13 b 4 13 9 13 13 13 b 13 9 13 4 13 0 {\p0}
{\pos(632,192)}{\fad(1000,0)}{\c&H00FEFEDB\t(0,2500,\c&H00D8D021)}瑞克与莫蒂
{\pos(617.333,622)}{\fad(500,0)}电波诚译
{\pos(617.333,666)}{\fad(500,0)}第一季 第四集
{\fn方正喵呜体}{\fs70\c&H20F0FF&\b1}电波字幕组 欢迎您的加入\N{\fs34}\N{\fs65\b0}官方网站:www.dbfansub.com\N{\fs34}\N{\fs65\b0}新浪微博:@电波字幕组
这做工真是渣
T-t-t-this is just sloppy craftsmanship.
嗨 Rick
Hey, Rick.
看呀 今天天可真好呀 是吧
Boy, sure is really especially beautiful out there today, huh?
没错 Morty
oh, yes, Morty.
简直好得不可思议 是吧
I-it's almost unbelievable, Isn't it?
是啊
Yeah, you know?
空气格外清新
There's something about the air
阳光分外明媚
And just the way the sunshine is.
没错 伙计 没错
uh, sure, buddy. Yeah.
当然 棒极了
Sure. B-brilliant.
我简直都要信了
Very convincing.
什么信了
Wha convincing?
哇 还能实时应答啊 真棒
Oh. Responsive, too. In real time. I love it.
好吧
Uhh...okay.
我要去工作了
I'm going to work.
Morty 早上好
Morty, good morning.
爸 早上好
Dad, good morning.
我要去工作了 再见
I am going to work. Goodbye.
老妈怎么了
what's with mom?
老妈怎么了
oh, what's with mom?
你想说她举止很奇怪吗
So, you're saying that she's acting weird?
搞得这么精细 小心点哟
How sophisticated. Careful, guys.
别把中央处理器烧咯
You're gonna burn out the cpu with this one.
算了 Rick
Okay, you know what, Rick?
你今天也很奇怪
You'reacting weird, too.
随你怎么说 所谓的"Morty"
whatever, quote-unquote "Morty."
好吧
all right, well...
那放学见了
I'll see you after school.
哦 噢
Ow! Oof! Ugh!
该死
Damn it!
我没事 我没事
I'm all right. I'm okay.
谁来说说五乘以九等于多少
All right, who can tell me what 5 x 9 is?
{\fs38}Morty\NMorty?
我
uh, me?
五乘以九等于多少
What is 5 x 9?
等于
umm...you know, it's
呃 至少四十吧
Uhh...at least 40.
Morty 完全正确
Morty, that's exactly correct!
五乘以九等于至少四十
5 x 9 is at least 40!
上这儿来
Come up here.
你真棒 Morty
Whoo! Way to go, Morty!
同学们 这是我们最好的学生
Everybody, this is the best student.
今天你来当老师
I want you to be the teacher today.
教教我们 Morty
Teach us, Morty!
有意思
Interesting.
你们想让我教什么
W-w-w-what do you want me to teach you?
怎么制造浓缩暗物质啊
How do you make concentrated dark matter?
这是个好问题
Oh, that's a good question.
浓缩什么
concentrated huh?
浓缩暗物质
Concentrated dark matter
加速级星际航行所需的燃料
The fuel for accelerated space travel.
你知道要怎么制造吗
Now, do you know how to make it?
呃
umm...
说啊 Morty
Come on, Morty.
你的外公不是个科学家吗
Isn't your grandpa, like, a Scientist?
没错 但是 他和我说
oh, yeah, but, you know, he told me that
我不可以随便告诉别人
I shouldn't go around spouting off about,
他的科学研究之类的
you know, his science and stuff.
你肯定看见过他制作浓缩暗物质很多次吧
I bet you've seen him make concentrated dark matter a lot.
只要你告诉我们
You know, if you tell us,
我就当你的女朋友
I'll be your girlfriend.
是吗
Uh, y-you will?
机会难得啊 Morty
Seems like a rare opportunity, Morty.
Morty 快来
Morty, u-uh, come on.
家里有急事
There's a family emergency.
站住
Stop right there!
如果他走了 我就挂了他这科
If he leaves, I'm giving him an "F."
他不在乎
he doesn't care.
噢 天
aw, man!
Rick 我必须得回去
Rick, I have to go back!
我觉得我就要结婚了
I think I was about to get married!
喔
Ugh!
和我一起洗澡 Morty
take a shower with me, Morty.
什么
what?!
听我说 Morty
listen to me, Morty.
把衣服脱了过来洗澡
Get your clothes off and get in the shower right now.
相信我 Morty
Y-y-y-you got to trust me, Morty.
噢
ugh!
我会挂科的 Rick
I'm gonna get an "F" In class, Rick.
Morty 你没在上课
Morty, that's not class.
他也不是你的老师
T-t-t-that wasn't your teacher.
这也不是你的学校
This isn't your school.
这个世界也不是我们的世界
This entire world is not the world.
我们在一个外星飞船上的大型模拟舱里
We're inside a huge simulation chamber on an alien spaceship.
等等
wait a minute.
你在说什么
W-what are you talking about?
都是假的
it's all fake
Morty 全都是
Morty, all of it.
纳米级机器渲染 搞出来的假玩意儿 Morty
Nanobotic renderings, a bunch of crazy fake nonsense, Morty.
只有在淋浴间我才能跟你说
I couldn't say so until we got in the shower.
这里他们不会监视
They won't monitor us in here.
监视我们吗 谁
Monitor us?! W-who?!
宇宙骗子Z星人 Morty
Zigerion scammers, Morty
星系里最雄心勃勃却最失败的诈骗集团
The galaxy's most ambitious, least successful con artists.
幸运的是
You know, it's lucky for us
他们没法直视裸体
They're also really uncomfortable with nudity.
得了 Rick
Aw, come on, Rick.
如果今天大家都不正常
If everyone's just gonna be insane today,
至少我要和Jessica一起发疯
at least let me be insane with jessica.
不行 Morty
I can't let you do that, Morty.
还给我
Give it to me!
不行
No!
给我
You give it to me!
给我 Rick
G-g-give it! No, Rick!
天啦 长官
Oh, god, sir!
他们还是裸着的
They're still naked!
嗷
Ugh.
每隔五昆顿检查一次
Well, check every five quintons
等他们不裸了再通知我
And tell me when they're not.
我觉得该让Kevin来盯着 长官
I think we should make kevin look, sir.
什么 不
What?! No!
你干嘛这么说
W-w-why would you even say that?
长官 这边有情况
Uh, sir, we have a situation over here.
要是监视器里有鸡鸡的话 那必须是有情况 Stu
If there's a wiener on that monitor, i swear to god, Stu...
处理系统能耗大幅度增加
Something is drawing a lot of processing power.
等下 难怪
Oh, wait. No wonder.
模拟舱中还有另一个人类
There's another real human in the simulator.
好了 Jerry 重大推销会
Okay, Jerry big pitch meeting.
成败在此一举
Make-or-break time.
你一定行的
You can do this.
这是怎么回事
How did this happen?!
绑架部在干嘛
Where's the abductions department?
绑架部是按照定位部的指令行事的
Hey, man, abductions just follows the acquisition order.
别想推给定位部
Don't put this on acquisitions!
我们只定位没有被模拟的人
We only acquire humans that haven't been simulated!
模拟部是不会模拟已经被绑架了的人的 所以
Well, simulations doesn't simulate anybody that's been abducted, so...
哦 我明白了
Oh, I see! Oh, oh!
谁都没错
It was no one's fault.
好吧
Oh, okay.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
好了 没啥问题了
Well, then, problem solved.
等等 不对
Oh, wait no.
还是有另外一个人类在这里
There's still another human in here!
他是谁
Who is he?
Rick的女婿
Rick's son-in-law,
{\fs38}Jerry Smith\NJerry Smith.
到现在为止 他还没发现自己在模拟舱里
So far, he hasn't noticed he's in a simulation.
将他所在区域的处理功能降到5%
Well, cap his sector at 5% processing,
设置为自动模式
keep his settings on auto,
晚点再来应付他
and we'll deal with him later.
Rick Sanchez才是目标
Rick Sanchez is the target.
放轻松
Got to relax.
不过是个推销会
It's just a pitch.
放轻松
Got to relax.
这里是地球电台
This is earth radio.
接下来是 人类音乐
And now, here's...human music.
人类音乐 我喜欢
hmm. Human music. I like it.
{\fs38}Rick\NRick!
呜呃
uhp, uhp, uhp!
Morty 别拿手挡着小弟弟
Morty, keep your hands off your Ding-dong!
只有这样我们才能随便说话
It's the only way we can speak freely.
看看周围 Morty
Look around you, Morty.
你真以为这个世界是真的
Do you really think this world is real?
这么多粗劣的细节你要多傻才会看不出来
You'd have to be an idiot not to notice all the sloppy details.
看那人把面包夹在两个热狗中间
Look that guy's putting a bun between two hot dogs.
我不知道 Rick
I don't know, Rick.
我见过有人这么干的呀
I mean, I've seen people do that before.
看看那个老太太
well, look at that old lady.
拿狗链栓了个猫在散步
She's she's walking a cat on a leash.
Spencer太太一直这样啊 Rick
uh, Mrs. Spencer does that all the time, Rick.
别提Spencer太太行吗 Morty
look, I-I-I don't want To hear about mrs. Spencer, Morty!
她就一白痴
She's an idiot!
好吧 看那儿
All right, all right, there.
这个如何 Morty
W-what about that, Morty?
好吧 你赢了
Okay, okay, you got me on that one.
真的吗 Morty
oh, really, Morty?
你确定在现实生活中没见过这种的东西
Are you sure you haven't seen that somewhere in real life before?
不 没有
no, no.
我没见过
I haven't seen that.
果酱饼怎么会住在烤面包机里呢
I mean, why would a pop tart want to live inside a toaster, Rick?
那种地方对它们来说不是应该很恐怖吗
I mean, that would be, like, the scariest place for them to live.
对吧
You know what I mean?
你搞错重点了 Morty
you're missing the Point, Morty.
他怎么会开个带轮子的小烤面包机呢
Why would he drive a smaller toaster with wheels?
你的车会像你房子的缩小版吗
I mean, does your car look like a smaller version of your house?
不会
No.
那他们干嘛要这样啊
So, why are they doing this?
他们想干嘛
W-what do they want?
这不是明摆着的吗 Morty
well, that would be obvious to you, Morty,
只要你留点心就会注意到了
If you'd been paying attention.
美国总统在这儿
We got the president of the United States in here!
我们急需10cc的浓缩暗物质 不然他就要死了
We need 10cc of concentrated dark matter, stat, or he'll die!
浓缩暗物质
Concentrated dark matter?
他们在教室里也问起了这个
They were asking about that in class.
没错 那是 我发明的一种特殊燃料
yeah, it's a special fuel I invented
可以让你用最快的速度穿行宇宙
to travel through space faster than anybody else.
Z星人一直试图
These Zigerions are always trying
骗取我的机密
to scam me out of my secrets,
但这次 他们犯了个大错 Morty
But they made a big mistake this time, Morty.
他们把你牵扯了进来
They dragged you into this.
他们会付出代价的
Now they're gonna pay!
那你要 我们该怎么做
what do you w-w-what are we gonna do?
我们要比他们更奸诈 Morty
we'll scam the scammers, Morty.
让他们付出一切
And we're gonna take them for everything they've got.
美国的果农们
National apple farmers of America,
欢迎来到我们的广告公司
welcome to our ad agency.
我是Jerry Smith
I'm Jerry Smith.
好吧
All right.
让我们直奔广告展示
I'll just...get to the pitch.
一个简单的问题 先生们
Um, simple question, gentlemen,
什么是苹果
what are apples?
不好意思
excuse me.
什么是苹果
What are apples?
苹果是食物
Apples are food.
那么 我们何时需要食物呢
And...when do we need food?
想吃东西的时候
When we're hungry.
因此 我将新标语介绍给你们
With that, I give you your new slogan!
{\pos(814.4,609.6)\3c&H9D6156&\b1\4c&H26262D&}想要苹果吗?{\b0}
说点什么啊
Well, say something!
你们喜欢吗
Do you like it?
是的
Yes.
真的
you do?
是的
yes.
所以 我成功了
so...I sold it?
我把这个创意卖出去了
I sold the idea?
是的
yes.
天哪 谢谢
oh, my god! Thank you!
- 谢谢  - 不用谢
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
嗨
hey!
我刚刚卖出了我的第一个广告
I just sold my first pitch!
慢着点
Slow down!
不错哟
Lookin' good.
干得好
My man!
你好
hello.
猜猜谁刚把苹果广告创意卖出去了
Guess who just sold the apples campaign.
谁刚刚把苹果广告创意卖出去了
who just sold the Apples campaign?
我
me!
所以这不是抄袭"有牛奶吗"(著名广告标语)
I guess it wasn't a rip-off of "Got milk?" after all.
某人是大错特错了啊
Guess someone was wrong.
是的
yes.
原谅你了 因为现在
well, all is forgiven, because right now,
我已经像东海岸灯塔一样一柱擎天了
I've got an erection the size of an east coast lighthouse,
我正要回家来和我美丽的老婆一起分享呢
And I'm coming home to share it with my beautiful wife.
好的
okay.
真的
Wait, really?
是的
yes.
太棒了
yes!
10分钟后见
See you in 10 minutes!
嘿
Hey!
我就要去和我老婆做爱了
I'm going to make love to my wife!
不错哟
Lookin' good.
慢着点
Slow down!
好样的
My man!
天哪 Rick
aw, geez, Rick.
这个计划真的好吗
I-I don't know if I like this plan, you know?
人一多 我就总觉得好紧张
I mean, crowds, t-t-t-they have a tendency to make me really nervous.
Morty 别怕
Morty, relax.
外面只不过是堆二进制代码
It's just a bunch of 1s and 0s out there.
没事的
You're gonna be fine.
跟着我来就行
Just follow my lead.
哟 DJ 节奏打起来
Yo, deejay, drop that beat.
啊噢 Morty
Uh-oh, Morty.
我们这么赞的说唱表演
This crowd looks too small
这人也来的太少了
for one of our famous rap concerts.
这我们还怎么表演我们的新歌
I don't think we can perform our new song,
"浓缩暗物质配方"
"The recipe for Concentrated dark matter,"
就这么点人
for a crowd this tiny.
你说的对 Rick
you got that right, Rick.
这还差不多
now that's more like it!
Morty 走着
Morty, here we go.
每个人都说"嘿哟"
Let me hear everybody say "Hey-oh!" Yeah!
所有女士请说"耶"
All the ladies say, "Yeah!"
所有超过30岁的人 用你们的手做这个动作
Everybody over 30, do this with your hands!
所有穿红衣服的人
Everybody with a red shirt,
上下蹦
jump up and down!
嗯嗯嗯
mm. Mm. Mm.
就这样 别动
Yeah, don't move.
嗯 嗯 唔嗯
Mm, mm, mm, mm!
嗯
Mm!
名字以"L"开头的非西班牙裔
name begins with an "L" who isn't hispanic,
绕圈子 圈数等于你们的年龄平方根的十倍
walk in a circle the same number of times as the square root of your age times 10!
快跑 Morty
Run, Morty!
趁着系统还没重启
Before the system reboots!
耶 喜欢这样么
yeah! You like that?
现在知道我的厉害了吧
Now who's unremarkable?
你想要苹果吗
You hungry for apples?
你 想要 苹果吗
Are you hungry...for...apples?!
哦 天哪
Oh, my god.
这是我有生以来最棒的一场爱爱了
That's the best sex I've ever had in my life.
这 这也太棒了
It's...it's...too good.
我配不上这个 Beth
I don't deserve this, Beth.
我是个骗子
I'm a fraud.
天 Rick
oh, man, Rick!
我们要跑哪儿去
W-w-w-where we running to?
跑出模拟舱 Morty
Out of the simulation, Morty.
通常来讲 模拟舱的运行类似跑步机
Normally, the chamber operates like a treadmill,
随着我们的移动 身后的虚拟世界会不断消失
with the virtual world disappearing
新渲染的空间会出现在我们眼前
behind us and being rendered in front of us as we move through it,
但如果它当机了 Morty
but while it's frozen, Morty,
我们就可以到达边界了
we can get to The edge.
快来吧
Here we go.
我的天啊
holy crap!
快点 Morty
come on, Morty.
长官 他们穿过边界了
Sir, they're over the edge.
没错
Yes, they are.
正如 计划 所料
Just...as...planned.
咱这心理操纵(mindfuck)玩得妙啊
Oh, this is going to be such a mind [beep].
到了中控室好好盯着点 Morty
keep your eyes peeled for the central processing room, Morty.
看看我们怎么耍这群傻子
That's how we're gonna scam these idiots.
嘿 Rick 如果你比这群外星人聪明那么多
so, hey, why do these aliens keep coming after you,
为啥他们还一直追着你不放啊
Rick, if you're so much smarter than them?
他们就是有这种执念
it's an obsession for them at this point.
这么多年来
The zigerions have been
Z星人一直想证明他们比我聪明 Morty
trying to outsmart me for years, Morty.
每次我都比他们棋高一着
Every time they do, I'm one step ahead of them.
啊哈
Aha!
到了
Here we go.
{\b1\pos(942.4,72)}中央处理器→
{\pos(803.2,467.2)\b1}←逃生舱{\b0}
能拿多少处理器就拿多少 Morty
Grab as many processors as you Can carry, Morty.
这群人没什么本事
These guys aren't good at much,
做芯片倒是有一套
But they're reallygood at making these chips.
我抓太多啦 都快拿不了啦
I've got so many, I can barely hold them all.
看呐 看我
Look at-look at this.
哎呀 掉了一个
Oops. I dropped one.
别担心 Morty
don't worry about it, Morty.
这玩意儿有的是 小笨蛋
There's plenty of them, you little goofball.
过来 Morty 噢 抓到你啦
Come here, Morty! Oh, I gotcha!
行啦 别闹啦 Rick
come on, quit it, Rick!
别闹啦
Quit it!
小家伙 时不时闹一下没啥错的
nothing wrong with just a little bit of horseplay every now and then, little fella.
哇哦 真没想到 居然这么容易
wow. What do you know? Huh. That was easy.
完全没错
totes malotes, dawg.
都有点不敢相信了
just kind of hard to believe, you know?
没啥不信的 Morty
believe it, Morty.
我又把能拿的全拿走然后远走高飞啦
And once again, I'm flying away with everything I can carry,
Z星人从我这儿什么都没搞到
and the Zigerions got nothing of mine.
Marklevitz先生 能和您谈谈吗
Mr. Marklevitz, do you have a Minute to talk?
好啊
yes.
我是个骗子
look, I'm a fraud.
我们面对事实吧
I mean, let's face it
"想要苹果吗"是我抄的"有牛奶吗"
"Hungry for apples" Is just a rip-off of "Got milk?"
简直如出一辙
It's almost identical.
是的
yes.
好吧
okay.
我活该
I deserve that.
我这就去卷铺盖卷
Umm...I guess...i'll just pack up my desk.
好的
yes.
噢 天哪
oh, my god.
等会儿 不对
Wait. You know what?! No!
编牛奶广告的那群人又没为简单反问句申请专利
The milk people don't have a patent on simple rhetorical questions!
"想吃苹果吗"和"有牛奶吧" 没一个字是一样的
There's not even a single word in "Hungry for apples" That's Shared by "Got milk?"
我写的是一个完全不同的广告语
It's a completely different slogan.
完全不同
It's different!
我不该走人
And I shouldn't be fired.
我该升职
I should be promoted!
是的
yes.
耶
yeah!
等等 真的吗
Wait. Really?
是的
Yes!
棒
yes!
虽然这条广告语是衍生出来的
I mean, I'm it may be derivative,
但这是公司这么久以来
but it's the most successful
最成功的一条广告语
campaign to come out of the agency in a long time.
是的
yes.
我倒不是说我该得个什么广告奖
i-I'm not saying it should win an award for commercials,
但完全可以有个专门颁给苹果广告的奖项的提名啊
but it could certainly be nominated for an award for commercials specifically about apples,
比如说 苹苹奖之类的
Like...an appley or something.
是的
yes.
真有和苹果品牌广告有关的奖项叫苹苹奖吗
is there really an award called the appley for apple-related ad campaigns?
是的
yes.
能提名我吗
could we nominate me?
是的
yes.
超赞啊
holy crap!
进来 Morty
get in, Morty.
我可以用这些处理器
I'm gonna be able to use these processors
搞点真正重大的科学发明
to make some real important science stuff.
哈 我应该输对了啊
Huh. I thought I entered the code right.
哇 这是什么啊
Wha well, what's this?
这是怎么回事
W-what could this possibly be?
因为看起来你们在模拟舱
Because it looks like you're inside a simulation...
里面的另一个模拟舱里
Inside a simulation.
你们还在我们的飞船上
You're still on the ship.
美梦破灭
Game-day bucket go boom.
{\an8}{\fs36}出自一个肯德基广告
长官 呃
Sir, the, uh,
您和医生之前预约的
doctor's appointment to examine
检查您肛门瓣的变色情况
the discoloration on your butthole flaps was
声音太大了 Cynthia
Too loud, Cynthia.
而且你说的太具体了
Too loud and too specific.
呃
uhh...
我们早就知道
We've known how to make
怎么制造浓缩暗物质了
concentrated dark matter for a long time.
不过现在嘛 我们 还知道了
But now we also know
你传说中的保险箱密码 Rick Sanchez
the code to your fabled safe, Rick Sanchez!
你所有最珍贵的秘密
All your most valuable secrets
马上就是我们的了
will now be ours!
是吗 我会在你们之前赶到家
uh, yeah, until I get home before you
然后把密码改了
and change the combination,
蠢货
you bunch of Idiots!
所以你永远也回不了家了
That is why you're never getting home.
给我抓起来
Get them!
快跑 Morty
Run, Morty!
噢老天啊
oh, my god!
{\fs36\b1\3c&HFF8100&\4c&H101410&\frx0\fry22\org(567.733,375.2)\pos(549.867,214.401)\frz17.83}关闭重力开关{\b0}
啊
Ow!
{\org(628,325.334)\frx6\fry344\frz350.1\b1\fs40\3c&H765B1D&\4c&H121215&\pos(591.999,215.734)}开启重力开关{\b0}
{\org(677.334,694.666)\frx6\fry0\pos(700,113.333)\b1}第七十五届
{\org(677.334,694.666)\frx6\fry0\pos(697.333,177.333)\b1\3c&H906025&\2c&H994D21&}苹苹奖
不得不说 今天早上
I got to tell you, this morning,
我都不知道还有这个奖
I didn't even know this award existed.
现在我居然拿着奖杯
Now I'm holding one.
呃
And...um...
我想说
Look, I want to say that today
今天是我一生中最美好的一天
was the best day of my life...
但其实它的意义远高于此
But...the truth is, it's it's more meaningful than that.
好样的
My man!
谢谢您
yes. Thank you, sir.
我的人生 终于 完整了
I...am...finally complete!
好 好 好 好样的
My my my my man!
啊啊
aah!
搞什么
What the hell?!
不要啊
No.
- Jerry  - 爸
- Jerry?!  - Dad!
你在这儿干啥呢
what are you doing Here?
你怎么穿的像个服务生似的
W-why are you dressed like a Waiter?
算了 没时间了 快跑
Screw it. We don't have time. Come on.
不要啊
no!
{\be1\pos(621.333,350.667)}{\pos(625.333,392)\3c&H24A775&\b0\fs48}{\fs45\t(\fs60)}逃生舱{\b1}
{\be1}{\pos(576,298.667)\3c&H1C1D97&\3a&H00&}研发部
{\pos(689.334,553.334)\3c&H4141AD&}禁区
啊啊啊啊
ohhhhh!
啊
aah!
啊
Oof!
有点儿男人样 Jerry
man up, Jerry!
可能得要你来操作激光炮
I may need you to work the lasers.
天啊 他们马上就要追上来了 Rick
Oh, man! They're hot on our tail, Rick!
看来他们确实有浓缩暗物质
I guess they really do have concentrated dark matter.
你也知道怎么制造的 对吧 Rick
well, you know how to make it, too, right, Rick?
是的
yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
去轮机舱看看
Uh, check the engine room.
我们需要铯 深成夸克
We just need cesium, plutonic quarks,
还有一瓶水
and bottled water.
齐了 Rick
it's all here, Rick!
哇 Morty 运气太好了
wow, Morty. Lucky break.
把那个桶拿过来
Grab that bucket.
好 两份深成夸克
Okay, two parts plutonic quarks,
一份铯
One part cesium.
好的
okay. Uh-huh.
好了
All right.
现在把水全倒进桶里
Now empty the water bottle into the bucket
再把混合物全倒进燃料箱
and pour it all into the fuel tank
然后我们就能逃出去了
so we can get the hell out of here!
你干啥呢 Morty
What are you doing, Morty?!
没时间了
There's no time!
噢 不是吧
oh, no.
到底
what the
不要啊
no!
天哪 Rick
Oh, my god, Rick.
你是有多蠢啊
How dumb are you?
你是在模拟出的模拟舱
You're inside a simulation... of a simulation...
模拟出的另一个模拟舱里
Inside another giant simulation!
我们从来没有过浓缩暗物质的配方
W-we never had the recipe for concentrated dark matter.
但是现在有了
But we do now!
现在有了 蠢货
We do now, sucka!
你们模拟了我外孙的生殖器
You simulated my grandson's genitalia?!
你们这群畜生
Y-y-you bunch of diabolical sons of bitches!
Kevin为了监管这项工程可是费了不少劲儿呢
Kevin fought real hard to supervise that project.
说好了不告诉别人的
You said you weren't gonna tell anyone!
这个梗我这辈子都摆脱不掉了是吗
I'm never gonna live this down, am I?
好吧 好吧
all right. Okay.
好吧 你厉害 你狠
All right, great. Wonderful.
你赢了 我们现在能回家了不
You win. Can we go home now?
我不知道 能吗
I don't know. Can you?
哈 赞
Ha! Nice.
好了 好了
Okay, okay.
把这个好骗的傻瓜送上航天机
Show this gullible turd to his shuttle.
没他什么事儿了
I'm done with him.
噢 等下 拍张照
Oh, wait. Let me get a picture.
哎哟 看他的表情
Aww. Look at his face.
他还在琢磨自己是不是在模拟舱里呢
He's trying to figure out if he's in a simulation still.
是吧 Rick
Are you, Rick?
是吧
Are you?
不是
You're not.
还是说 是呢
Or are you?
噢 还 还有
Oh, a-and, by the way,
我的肛门瓣可没变色
I don't have discolored butthole flaps.
那是模拟的一部分
That was part of the simulation.
噢
Oh.
呃 长官 那我是不是要取消预约
Uh, sir, should I cancel that appointment, then?
对啊 当然取消
Yeah! Of course you should!
不 留着
No, keep it.
可以的话 提到上面去
Move it up, actually, if you can.
嘿 Jerry 别担心嘛
Hey, Jerry, don't worry about it.
就算你人生中最有意义的一天是 都是最低性能的模拟又怎么样呢
So what if the most meaningful day of your life was a simulation operating at minimum capacity?
是吗 Rick 这些人也把你耍了
you know what, Rick? Those guys took you for a ride, too.
你还是尊重一下宇宙里的蠢人吧
You should try having a little respect for the dummies of the universe,
既然你也是其中之一
now that you're one of us.
也许你说得对 Jerry
maybe you're right, Jerry.
也许你说得对
Maybe you're right.
好了大伙儿
All right, everybody.
两份深成夸克
Two parts plutonic quarks...
一份铯
One part cesium...
还有 很抱歉之前对大家大吼大叫
A-and listen, I'm sorry for yelling earlier.
你们是最棒的员工
I-I couldn't ask for a better Staff.
我爱你们 我也爱你们的家人
I love you guys, and I love all your families.
最后的原料
And the final ingredient...
啊
whoa!
搞什么啊
What the hell?!
发生了什么
W-what happened back there?
Jerry 不然你去问问全宇宙最聪明的人吧
why don't you ask the smartest people in the universe, Jerry?
噢对 没法问了
Oh, yeah. You can't.
他们都被炸飞了
They blew up.
{\an8}{\fs36}Gerry Rafferty《Baker Street》
那么
so...
怎么样
What do you think?
你被解雇了
You're fired.
啥
wha
但这个创意已经通过了最先进的模拟测试了
But t-this idea was tested in a state-of-the-art simulation.
那这模拟有够烂的
Well, then, it was a terrible Simulation.
滚出去
Get out.
天 这种人是怎么能回家和他老婆做爱的
Man, how does a guy like that go home and have sex with his wife?
嘿 Morty
hey, Morty.
干啥啊
what?
嘿 小伙子
hey, little buddy.
你感觉怎 怎么样
H-h-how you doing in here right Now?
天 Rick
aw, geez, Rick.
你来干啥啊
What are you doing, man?
你你你是个好孩子 Morty
y-y-you're a good kid, Morty.
你真是个人人人物 Morty
Y-you're a real l-little c-character, Morty.
唉
oh, boy.
我今天很不顺 Morty
you know, I had a really rocky road today, M-Morty.
你是我的小伙伴 是吧
You're my little friend, aren't You?
我们一起玩得很开心 是吧 Morty
We had some good times together, Huh, M-Morty?
我们 你是个真正的英雄
We... You're a real true hero out in the field.
你是个
You're a li
你是顶梁柱啊 对吧 Morty
You're a real trouper, huh, M-m-Morty?
你喝酒了吗 Rick
have you been Drinking, Rick?
我真的挺欣赏你的
T really appreciate You, Morty.
好好吧 知道了
o-okay, cool.
好好吧 Rick
A-all right, Rick
你个小狗崽子
you little son of a bitch!
你是模拟出来的吗
Y-y are you a simulation?!
哼 你是模拟出来的吗
Huh?! Are you a simulation?!
不 我不是啊
no! No! No!
你个小狗崽子
you little son of a Bitch!
对对对不起 Morty
i-I-I'm sorry, Morty.
你是个好 你是个好孩子 Morty
Y-you're a good.. You're a good kid, Morty.
我去
geez!
你是个好 你是个好孩子
y-you're a good... you're a good kid.
噢天
oh, my god!
搞什么啊
w-w-what the hell?
人生真艰难
What a life.

