
{\an8\fs32\fad(800,800)\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H666562&\b1}{\fn时尚中黑简体}翻译: 咣当 小萌 遥望 阿朽
{\c&HFFFFFF&\b1\3c&H666562&}{\an8\fs32\fad(800,800)}{\fn时尚中黑简体}校对: 史努比哒
{\c&HFFFFFF&}{\an8\fs32\fad(800,800)\b1\3c&H666562&}{\fn时尚中黑简体}后期: 小萌
{\c&HFFFFFF&\an8}{\fs32\fad(800,800)\b1\3c&H666562&}{\fn时尚中黑简体\b1}压制: 凯撒
{\fs34}{\p1\c&H96955E&\fscx4200\fscy410\an8\fad(800,800)\pos(642,0)}m 0 0 b 0 0 0 0 0 0 b 0 0 0 0 0 0 b 0 4 0 9 0 13 b 4 13 9 13 13 13 b 13 9 13 4 13 0 {\p0}
{\pos(632,192)}{\fad(1000,0)}{\c&H00FEFEDB\t(0,2500,\c&H00D8D021)}瑞克与莫蒂
{\pos(617.333,622)}{\fad(500,0)}电波诚译
{\pos(617.333,666)}{\fad(500,0)}第一季 第十集
{\fn方正喵呜体}{\fs70\c&H20F0FF&\b1}电波字幕组 欢迎您的加入\N{\fs34}\N{\fs65\b0}官方网站:www.dbfansub.com\N{\fs34}\N{\fs65\b0}新浪微博:@电波字幕组
爸爸 你猜明天是什么日子
So, dad, guess what tomorrow is.
马丁·路德·金诞辰
Martin Luther King Jr.'s birthday.
- 不是 好吧 也许是  - 就是
- No. Well, it...might be. - It is.
好吧 但是 明天也是你回归我们生活的一周年纪念日
Fine. But also, tomorrow is your one-year anniversary back in our lives.
我要给你做飞碟形煎饼
I'm gonna make you flying-saucer-shaped pancakes.
哦 没这个必要 Beth 正常煎饼就行了
Oh, t-t-there's no need to do that, Beth. Regular pancakes are fine.
哦上帝
Oh, my God!
这是怎么回事
Oh, what is happening?!
周年纪念快乐 爸爸
Happy anniversary, dad.
哦 我懂了
Oh, I get it.
正常煎饼就已经像飞碟了
Regular pancakes are already shaped like flying saucers.
好吃 其实为了感谢你一直忍受我 我应该给你做早饭的
Mmm. I-I should be making you breakfast for putting up with me.
你应该给我们弄一整家餐厅
You should be making us a whole restaurant.
胡说 有你在身边 我们再开心不过了
Nonsense. We couldn't be happier to have you around.
我只希望能多陪陪你(看见更多的你)
I just wish I got to see more of you.
地球空间C-137的Rick Sanchez
Rick Sanchez of Earth dimension c-137,
你因对平行空间的其他Rick犯下的罪行
you are under arrest for crimes against alternate Ricks
而被跨维度Rick委员会批准逮捕
by the authority of the Trans-Dimensional Council of Ricks.
- 嘿 搞什么鬼  - 冻住Jerry
- Hey! What the heck?! - Neutralize the Jerry.
等等 别 我可以
Wait! No! I'll...
爸爸
Dad!
- 爸爸  - Rick
- Dad! - Rick!
大家别紧张
Everybody, relax.
我认识这些混蛋 我就是这些混蛋
If I know these a-holes, and I am these a-holes,
他们只想把我拽到他们那傻逼俱乐部
they just want to haul me to their stupid clubhouse
问几个浪费时间的问题
and waste my time with a bunch of questions.
咱们快把这事儿结了吧
Let's get it over with.
- 带上他的Morty  - 哦天
- Bring his Morty. - Oh, man.
别把我的Morty卷进来
Leave my Morty out of this.
你在拒绝加入委员会的时候就已经失去了说这话的权利
You lost the right to have a say in these things when you refused to j-join the Council.
Jerry怎怎怎么办
W-w-w-what about Jerry?
你们至少把我女儿的白痴解冻了行吗
Will you at least unfreeze my daughter's idiot?
给你任何东西
...give you anything!
我收藏了很多珍稀古董钱币 拜托别伤害我
I have a rare antique-coin collection! Just don't hurt me!
好吧 可能不是古董 但也是限量版铸币呢
Okay, maybe not antique, but it was a limited minting.
上面印的小R2-D2取代了乔治华盛顿
They have little R2-D2s instead of George Washington.
{\an8\fs38}R2-D2 星球大战系列中出现的机器人角色
咱们儿子被拐走了
Our son's been abducted!
我买那些硬币你一直很不满
You hate me for buying those coins!
天哪 Rick 这是什么地方
Geez, Rick, w-what is this place?
Rick们的大本营
The citadel of Ricks.
这是Rick委员会的秘密总部
It's the secret headquarters for the Council of Ricks.
Rick委员会
Council of Ricks?
{\an8\fs38}戏仿The Council of Reeds 由多个平行宇宙的Reed Richards组成的委员会(神奇四侠里的神奇先生)
你知道的 Morty 我在宇宙中树敌无数 他们视我的天才为威胁
As you know, Morty, I've got a lot of enemies in the universe that consider my genius a threat,
包括星系恐怖分子 下星系独裁者 和多数跨星系政府
galactic terrorists, a few sub-galactic dictators, most of the entire intergalactic government.
只有是有蠢驴的地方 就有人看我不爽
W-w-wherever you find people with heads up their asses, someone wants a piece of your grandpa,
而且不同平行宇宙里不同版本的我都是这样
and a lot of versions of me on different timelines had the same problem,
所以有几千个我傻逼一样地想凑在一起
so a few thousand versions of me had the ingenious idea of banding together
像牛群 鱼群
like a herd of cattle or a school of fish
或者在雅虎知道上回答问题的人一样
or those people who answer questions on Yahoo! answers.
嘿 居然有牛仔版的我
Hey! What do you know? It's a cowboy version of me.
你真是没见过世面
Geez, you're easy to impress.
没错 大多数时间线都有个Rick 而大多数Rick都有个Morty
Yeah, most timelines have a Rick, and most Ricks have a Morty.
这地方就是个你和我的名人录
This place is a real who's who of who's you and me.
快用Morty闪耀胸章把你无聊的旧Morty
Turn your boring, old Morty into a f...
变成热辣的时尚宣言吧
hot fashion statement with some Morty dazzlers.
嘿 看这个
Hey, check this out.
- 给我Morty  - 傻死了
- Show me the Morty. - Dumb.
打扰一下 先生 你为你的Morty投保了吗
Excuse me, sir, is your Morty insured?
- 要知道 每年都有成百上千的Morty受伤  - 滚
- You know, every year, hundreds of Mortys are injured... - Back off!
我不喜欢这地方
Not my cup of tea, this place.
我认为作为一个Rick而存在 重点就是作为"一个"Rick
I say the point of being a Rick is being A Rick.
把你的反Rick言论留给Rick委员会听吧 恐怖Rick分子
Save your anti-Rick speech for the Council of Ricks, terror-Rick.
嘿 把你的Rick规则留给Rick小绵羊吧 蠢猪Rick
Hey, save your Rick rules for the sheep-Ricks, Rick-pig.
[哔]我啊 哥们
[Bleep] me, pal.
[哔]你 不不不不不 [哔]我啊
[Bleep] you? No, no, no, no, no, [Bleep] me.
把全息图呈上来
Bring up the holograms.
有27个Rick在自己的平行空间里被残忍杀害
27 Ricks brutally murdered in their own timelines,
空前猖獗的对Rick的屠杀
an unprecedented Rick-icidal epidemic.
你还有什么可说的 地球C-137的Rick
What say you, Earth Rick c-137?
你觉得是我干的
You think I did this?
为什么每次有Rick踢到了脚趾总是我先被抓来
Why am I the first Rick you pull in every time a Rick stubs his toe?
你有不和委员会合作的前科
You have a history of non-cooperation with the Council.
没错 那个以前被称作Rick的科学家不也是吗
Yeah, so does the scientist formerly known as Rick.
为为为什么他没被抓过来铐住
W-w-w-w-w-why isn't he here in handcuffs?
因为他也死了
Because he's dead, too!
你还想让我们审问谁 你最符合凶手的特征
Who else would you have us question? You fit the profile.
在所有中央有限曲线上的Rick中
Of all the Ricks in the central finite curve,
你是反抗者 离群者
you're the malcontent, the rogue.
我只是Rick 在组成这个愚蠢的联盟以前 你们也是
I'm the Rick, and so were the rest of you before you formed this stupid alliance.
你们想免受政府的迫害 于是你们自己变成了愚蠢的政府
You wanted to be safe from the government, so you became a stupid government.
所以我比这里的每一个Rick都更像真正的Rick
That makes every Rick here less Rick than me.
尽情议论吧 混蛋们
Yeah, murmur it up, D-bags.
不好意思 家里还有涂了糖浆的煎饼等着我呢
Now, if you'll excuse me, I've got pancakes back home with syrup on top of them.
马上吸收的糖浆就会把煎饼变成恶心的浆糊了
They're about to hit that critical point of syrup absorption that turns the cakes into a gross paste,
我不想像Andy Rooney一样
and I hate to get all Andy Ronney about it,
{\an8\fs38}Andy Ronney 美国电视新闻节目《60分钟时事杂志》主持人之一
但我认为我们都喜欢一碟松软的糖浆蛋糕
but I think we all like fluffy disks of cake with syrup on top,
而且我们都希望被指责的时候对方拿出证据
and I think we also like to be accused of crimes when there's evidence!
用加拿大人的话来说 后会有期
So, as they say in Canada, peace oot!
证据 好主意 扫描他的传送门枪
Evidence! Good idea. Scan his portal gun!
哦 拜托 不要看别人的传送门枪历史记录啊
Oh, come on. Don't look at another man's portal-gun history.
谁都去过奇怪的地方
We-we all go to weird places.
没错 但似乎只有你一个人去过所有
Yes, but it appears you alone have been going to
谋杀发生的平行世界和其中谋杀发生的地点
the exact timelines and locations in which the murders occurred.
什么 那太不合Rick理了 我显然是被陷害的
What?! That's Rick-diculous! I'm obviously being set up.
地球C-137的Rick 委员会判处你受刑于极苦机械
Earth Rick c-137, the Council of Ricks sentences you to the machine of unspeakable doom,
你的意识和无意识将被互换
which swaps your conscious and unconscious minds,
使你一切的憧憬都毫无意义 让你所知的一切都无法触及
rendering your fantasies pointless while everything you've known becomes impossible to grasp.
而且 每过十秒它就会扎一次你的蛋蛋
Also, every 10 seconds, it stabs your balls.
我不想再听了
I've heard enough.
快跑 Morty
Run, Morty!
不不 没叫你
Unh-unh. Not you.
不
No!
啊
Aaaah!
哦 哦
Oh! Oh!
你好 我想点一大份人 加量
Yeah, I'd like to order one large person with extra people, please.
白人 不不不不 黑人 再加一半西班牙裔
White people. No, no, no, no. Black people. And Hispanic on half.
{\pos(459.2,96)\frx0\fry8\fs48\frz350.8}欢迎来到油腻腻老奶奶世界
{\fs48\frz354.9\frx2\fry4\pos(425.6,334.4)}人口: 可多了 亲爱的
你好 我想点一大份沙发椅 多加点椅量
Yes, I'd like to order one large sofa chair with extra chair, please.
高脚椅 不不不不 躺椅 和半个轮椅
High chair. No, no, no, no. Recliner. And wheelchair on half.
- 哪个门都有可能  - 混...
- They could have gone into anyone of these. - Son of a...
- 天啊  - 哦天  - 我们跟丢了
- Oh, geez. - Oh, man! - We lost 'em.
你好 我想点一大份电话 加量
Yeah, I'd like to order one large phone with extra phones, please.
手机 不不不不 旋转式电话 和半个公用电话
Cellphone. No, no, no, no. Rotary. And pay phone on half.
这够他们忙一阵的了
That'll keep 'em busy for a while.
他们肯定搞错了吧
Those guys were wrong right?
你不会杀掉你自己的 那些自己
You would not kill yourself... yourselves.
当然不会 Morty
Of course not, Morty.
这对我有啥好处
How could that profit me?
但是的确有人在杀Rick们
But someone out there is killing Ricks,
在我们洗清罪名之前 委员会不会善罢甘休
and the council ain't gonna stop thinking it's me until we clear our names
得找到真正的Rick杀手
by finding the real Rick-Killer.
我害怕 Rick
I'm scared, Rick.
我们是不是该回家准备点武器 就像《末日生存者》那节目一样
Maybe we should go home and stockpile weapons, like that show "Doomsday Preppers."
{\an8\fs38}国家地理频道电视节目
那不是我的风格 Morty
Not really my style, Morty.
而且 家里估计已经全是Rick了
Besides, your home is most likely swarming with Ricks by now.
听好了 Jerry
All right, listen, Jerry.
如果Rick打电话来 这设备能追踪到他的位置
If Rick calls, this device is gonna trace his location.
你只需要把时间拖够30秒
You just got to keep him on the phone for 30 seconds or longer.
谁想喝柠檬汁
Who wants lemonade?
噢 太好了
Oh, yeah. Mmm!
哦 好喝
Oh! Delicious!
Beth 你真贤惠
Beth. You're a treasure.
在我的世界里也有一个像你一样的Beth 只不过
I have a Beth just like you in my reality, except you know what?
她没有你那么美丽动人
She's not as brilliant or attractive.
哦 谢谢
Aw. Thank you.
她做到了 做到了
Oh! She did! She did it!
喂
H-hello?
嗨 Jerry 我是Rick
Hey, Jerry, it's Rick.
Rick 嗨
Rick! Hey.
你好啊
What's, what's up?
听着 风声太紧 我们没地方可去
So, listen, the heat's on, and there's nowhere left to turn,
所以 Morty和我打算把飞船开进黑洞
so Morty and I are just gonna fly my spaceship into a black hole.
- 什么  - 你能接受得了吧
- What? - Is that cool with you, dawg?
Rick 不 Morty
Rick, no! Morty!!
追踪到了
We got it.
电话来自...
The call's coming from...
这间屋子
inside the house
瞅瞅他的表情 你真傻
Look at his face! You dummy!
真不敢相信我们女儿能嫁给你
Ugh. Can't believe our daughter married you.
太容易了
Too easy!
这帮Rick应该会浪费些时间逗Jerry玩
The Rick are probably gonna waste some time missing with Jerry.
他们起不了什么作用的
They won't be able to help themselves.
但是等他们玩够了 就会来找我们
But as soon as they get bored, they'll be onto us.
您点的电话蛤蜊和意大利电面配电话丸
Phones a la clams and phonesghetti with phone balls.
- 还需要什么  - 再多来点电话条
- Anything else? - Yeah, more phone sticks, please.
马上来 先生
Right away, sir.
你知道吗 Rick 当我第一次看到那么多Rick和Morty时
You know, Rick, when I first saw all those Ricks and Morty,
我在想 "天啊 我们的关系一下就不那么独特了"
I thought, "Gee, that kind of devalues our bond."
但是仔细想想 我们的关系一定非常特别
But then I realized it just means that our relationship must be pretty special
才能让我们跨越无数的时空紧紧相连
to span over all those different time lines.
只能是这样 你是一个掩护
Yeah, it's got to be that way. You're a camouflage.
掩护
Camouflage?
你在说什么 Rick
W-w-w-what are you talking about, Rick?
Rick的天才使得我们的脑电波非常独特且易追踪
Rick have a very distinctive and traceable brain wave due to our genius.
躲避敌人雷达的最好办法就是
The best way to hide from an enemy's radar is
在一个可以使脑电波互补的人身边 这样就无法被追踪了
to stand near someone with complementary brain wave that make ours invisible.
明白吗 当Rick和Morty在一起时
See, w-w-w-when a Rick I-is with a Morty,
天才的脑电波就被抵消了 因为你有 呃
the genius waves get canceled out by the, Uh...
...Morty脑电波
...Morty waves.
是因为我们的性格非常不同吗
Um... because o-our personalities are so different?
哦 妈的
Oh, shit, dawg.
我的传送枪被人远端入侵了
My portal gun was hacked pemotely, Morty
很明显就是真凶 他想陷害我
Obviously by the real killer, to frame me.
但是我能追踪他的信号
But I was able to track the signal.
快 我们走
Come on. Let's go.
啊 噢
Uh-oh.
打扰了 我们追踪到一对极度危险的罪犯
Excuse me. We've tracked a pair of dangerous criminals
就在这里
to this exact location.
他们和我们长得一模一样
They look exactly like us,
为了避免混淆 我们用红叉
so in order to avoid confusion, I'm gonna mark us
标记自己
each with a red "X" right now.
这样的话 如果谁有枪
That ways, if someone has a gun and we both tell you
而我们都说杀掉另一个"我" 因为他才是那个坏人
to shoot the other one because they're the evil one,
你就知道是谁在说谎了
you'll know who's lying.
嗨 看那
Hey, check it out.
妈的
Damn it!
嗨 你还没给钱呢
Hey, you didn't pay your bill!
红叉 红叉
T-the red "X"! Red "X"!
嗨 还好那家宇宙折扣店 有这款实验室外套
Hey, it's a good thing that space outlet had lab coats
和你最爱的小黄体恤衫 是吧 Morty
and you favorite kind of shirt in stock, Huh, Morty?
对 Rick 你都说了好几遍了
Yeah, Rick, I-I heard you the first time.
你不用老说这个事儿了
You don't have to keep saying it over and over.
这地方真够偏僻的
Man, this place is way off the grid.
这家伙真不想让人发现
This guy does not want to be found.
如果这家伙是Rick 是不是他也需要用Morty来隐藏自己
Well, if he's a Rick, doesn't he just to stand by a Morty to hide?
Morty不就起这个作用吗
I mean, isn't that what Mortys are
人肉隐身衣
Human cloaking devices?
Morty 你这反应实在是有点小题大做了
Morty, you're making a bigger deal out of this than it is.
我的天啊 Rick 看
Oh, my god, Rick, look!
有好多人被绑起来 盖满了那栋建筑
There's a bunch of people strapped all over that building!
不是人 是Morty们
Not people, Morty. Mortys.
天啊
Oh, god!
为什么有人会这么干
W-w-why would somebody do this?
太残忍了
It's horrible!
想不被官僚体系的走狗发现 一个Morty足够了
Well, one Morty's enough to hide from the bureaucrats,
但你得用一个Morty矩阵 并且让他们极度痛苦
but you get- you get a whole matrix of Mortys and put them in agonizing pain,
才能瞒过其他的Rick [哔]
that creates a pattern that can hide even from other Ricks mother[Bleep]
我以前构想过一个类似的概念
I fiddled with a concept like this once.
理论上 Morty 只是理论上
On paper, Morty. On paper.
我是不会做这种事的 这就是粗劣的浪费和滥用
I wouldn't do this. It's barbaric overkill.
达到相同的效果 完全只需要
I mean, you could accomplish the same result with,
五个Morty和一个跨接电缆
like, five Mortys and a jumper cable.
这我也不会真做的
Which I also wouldn't do!
我只是想表示 他这技术太烂了
I'm just saying, it's bad craftsmanship.
咖啡时间
Coffee time!
好 哟 哟 哟
Yeah! Yo, yo, yo, yo!
就等这个呢
That's what I like to hear!
嗨 Jerry
Hi, Jerry.
别烦我 我在工作
Leave me alone. I'm working.
是吗 你是做什么的
Oh, you are? W-w-w-what do you do?
我是做广告的 待业中
I-I'm, I'm in between advertising jobs.
广告 哇
Advertising? Wow!
就是说 大家不知道自己应该买什么东西 你的工作就是帮助他们
So, people need help figuring out what to buy, and then you help them?
要更复杂一点
Well, it's a little more complicated than that.
你就是干这个的
Well, I mean, you do it,
而且你看起来干这行就很厉害
and you seem like a guy who really has it all together.
老兄 你是
Dude, are you,
你是在讽刺我 对吗
You're being a dick, right?
哦 天啊 不 不是
Oh, gosh, I-I hope not.
我一点都不想冒犯你
I-I-I wouldn't want to offend you in any way.
你真的是Rick吗
You're really a rick?
我当然是 就像我的Morty是一个Morty一样
Of course I am, just as much as my Morty's a Morty.
嗨 他长得好像《面具》里的Eric Stoltz
Hey, he looks a lot like Eric Stoltz from the movie "Mask."
{\an8\fs38}《面具》 1985年电影 Cher和Eric Stoltz均为主演
{\an8\fs38}故事主角是一个面部严重扭曲的年轻男孩
就是里面有雪儿的那部
You know, the one with Cher in it?
对的 Jerry
That's right, Jerry!
他来自的时空 所有的人长得都像Eric Stoltz的《面具》里的人
He-- he's from a reality where everyone is Eric Stoltz "Mask" people.
他是Eric Stoltz面具版Morty
He's Eric Stoltz mask Morty.
他是被分配给我的 因为我从来没有我自己的小孩
They assigned him to me because I never had any kids of my own.
但我如果有小孩
But if I did, boy,
我希望他们能像你一样聪明成功
I'd love them if they were as smart and as successful as you are, Jerry.
嗨 瞧啊
Hey, get a load of this.
Jerry在和傻瓜Rick聊天
Jerry's hanging out with doofus Rick.
你俩真配
This is perfect.
我不是傻瓜Rick
I'm not boofus Rick!
我是从J19-ZETA-7空间来的Rick
I'm Rick J19-ZETA-7!
噢 那个空间的人不都是吃屎长大的吗
Oh, is that the time line where everybody eats poop?
Jerry 你知道这家伙吃屎吗
Jerry, you know this guy eats poop, right?
嗨 我不吃屎
Hey, I don't eat poop!
你们总是欺负我
Y-You guys are always so mean to me.
我觉得我应该告诉你 Jerry
I guess it's only fair to tell you now, Jerry.
我是所有Rick当中最差劲的
I'm the worst Rick of them all.
谁说的 其他的你吗
According to who, other versions of you?
要说我这辈子如果明白了什么
If I've learned one thing,
不论你在人生中做什么决定
it's that before you get anywhere in life,
都不要听你自己的
you got to stop listening to yourself.
哇 你真是太有智慧了 Jerry
Wow. you really are wise, Jerry.
所以你才会做广告工作吧
I-I-I guess that's why you work in advertising.
你能这么想 你就已经是最棒的Rick了
The fact that you feel that way makes you the best Rick of them all.
你从来就没关心过我
You don't care about me at all!
我和你的外套没任何区别
I'm no different than that jacket you've got on!
或者是你的破传送枪
Y-y-y--o-or your stupid portal gun!
我就是个工具
I'm just a tool!
我 我 我就是个物件
I-I-I'm just an object!
你非要这么较真我也没办法 Morty
Hey, it's your choice to take it personally, Morty.
现在 看在上帝的份上 安静点吧
Now, for the love of god, be quiet.
咱们必须要先发制人
The point of this is to get the drop on the guy.
Rick 我告诉你
You know what, Rick? I'll tell you something!
我不只是个人肉护盾
I'm more than a human shield!
对 你说得非常对
Yeah, that's right. You are.
你是完美的 无可穿透的人体护甲 Morty
You're a perfect, impenetrable suit of human armor, Morty,
因为我有多聪明你就有多傻
because you're as dumb as I am smart,
所以当我说"闭嘴"时 你最好乖乖闭嘴
which is why when I say "shut up," it's really good advice.
全拜你所赐 Morty
Great, nice work, Morty.
看看你自己 C-137 你真是个难对付的客户
Ooh. Look at you, C-137. You, aren't you a tough customer.
慢慢鼓掌 没搞错吧(各种电影反派经典登场)
The slow clap? Really?
这有点被玩烂了吧 老兄
Kind of played out, dude.
在这个次元还没有
Not in this dimension, it isn't.
事实上 这就是我发明的 这里以前没人这么干过
In fact I invented it. Nobody else has ever even done it here before.
哎哟 真是好厉害呢
Well, La-di-da.
嘿 别学我
Hey, that's mine!
我不喜欢那个Rick的样子 Morty
I don't like the look of that Rick, Morty.
我们得逃出去
We got to escape.
我才不会帮你呢 Rick
I'm not gonna help you, Rick.
你是个怪物
Y-you're a monster.
别蛮不讲Rick理 Morty
Don't be Rick-diculous, Morty.
你能不能别这么说话了 很蠢的
W-will you stop saying that? It's stupid.
把他的Morty带走
Take his Morty away.
- 跟我走  - 好啊 高兴得很
- Come with me. - Yeah, gladly.
天哪 这些个Rick啊
Geez, man. Ricks, huh?
嘿 老兄 你好像知道这里是怎么运作的
Hey, man, you seem to know how this place works.
有没有什么方法可以关闭这些线路
Is there any way we could shut down that grid
放掉外面那些Morty
and rescue all those Mortys outside?
这样做毫无意义
It would be pointless.
Morty们根本没机会打败Rick
Mortys have no chance of defeating a Rick.
进去吧
In here.
多美啊 不是吗
Ah. Isn't it beautiful?
是啊是啊 就像梦幻庄园的发薪日
Yeah, yeah. Looks like payday at Neverland Ranch in here.
{\an8\fs38}梦幻庄园 曾是迈克尔杰克逊的私家游乐园和住所 财政状况不佳
叮
Zing!
他听懂了
That guy got it.
啊 啊 啊 Rick 安静
Unh-unh-unh, Rick, quiet.
别错过了我的交响曲
You're missing my symphony.
嘿 我觉得比蒙福之子的歌好听
Hey, I'll take it over Mumford & Sons. Zip!
{\an8\fs38}Mumford & Sons 英国民谣乐队 拿过第五十五届格莱美
这家伙真上道
This guy is on it!
他可不是在笑你的蠢笑话 Rick
He's not laughing at your dumb jokes, Rick.
那不过是他每隔10秒随意发出的声音
That's just a random noise it makes every 10 seconds.
看吧 Rick 你不像你想象的那么聪明
You see, Rick, you're not as clever as you think you are.
是我想让你找到我
I wanted you to find me.
我们没有多大的差别 你和我
We're not so different, you and I.
可不是嘛
Yeah, Duh!
看见这个了吗 Rick
See this right here, Rick?
我进行了大规模数字运算
I crunched the numbers.
然后列出了所有的Rick
I created a spectrum of all the Ricks.
我按照邪恶的程度来排列他们
I listed them out from most evil to least evil.
我在这里
Here's where I am.
看 你就在这里 Rick
And look it right here's where you are, Rick.
而这里这家伙 超级古怪
This guy right here, super-weird.
我懂了 你想让我跟你合作
I get it. So you want me to team up with you
去搞垮Rick议会 对吗
to take down the council of Ricks, right?
你就想干这个对吧
Is that where you're going with this?
因为我就会这么干
'Cause that's where I'd be going.
得了吧 我自己做得挺好的
Please. I think I'm doing pretty good on my own.
我只用把你大脑的内容下载下来
I'm simply gonna download the contents of your brain
然后杀了你
and then kill you.
好 如果我们加入一点硝酸钛
Okay, if we add a little more titanium nitrate
还有少量的氯化酒石酸盐
and just a tad of chlorified tartrate.
不用烤的巧克力蛋糕
Ovenless brownies!
嗯 嗯 太了不起了
Mmm. Mmm! It's incredible
天才的头脑能完成多么美妙的事啊 只要弄明白什么才是最重要的
What a gifted mind can accomplish when priorities are in order.
过奖了 不是我一个人的功劳 Jerry
Well, come on. I can't take all the credit, Jerry.
这是你的想法 来吧 Jerry
It was your idea. Come here, Jerry!
嘿 过来
Hey, come here.
我想给你看个东西
I-I want to show you something.
好 看 所有人因为我买了这个而嘲笑我
Okay, look, everybody makes fun of me getting these,
但是你是天才科学家 你觉得如何
but you're a genius scientist. What do you think?
总统头像的地方刻的是星球大战机器人
There's little R2-D2s where the George Washingtons should be.
这么说吧 Jerry 我不会告诉你说
You know Jerry, I'm not gonna tell you
这些东西会升值 或者保值
what these will increase in value or even hold there current value.
但是 你买这些东西就是因为你喜欢
The truth is, you bought them because you like them.
他们对你来说很有价值 这就够了
They have value to you. That's what matters.
你会在这待多久
How long are you staying?
直到我们找到你的Rick
Untill we find your Rick.
我已经找到了
I found mine.
已经找到了
I found mine.
救命
Help!
逃不出去的 孩子
There is no escape, my son.
我们可以在来世寻得宁静
We will find our peace in the next world.
那 你们就这么放弃了吗
So what Y-y-y-you're just gonna give up?
我们是屈从于本真Morty的神力
We're giving in to the power of the one true Morty.
总有一天 他会回来的
One day, he will return.
赞美本真Morty
Praise the one true Morty.
{\frz340.9\pos(720,520)\fs48\frx4\fry352}善美Morty
{\frz343.1\fs25\pos(833.6,316.4)}我觉得我们不该上这种网站
{\fs26\frx0\fry348\frz352.6\pos(544,222)}Morty 快看这个网页
好了 Morty们 听着
All right, Mortys, listen up.
我叫Morty Smith 来自地球空间C-137
My name is Morty Smith, from Earth dimension C-137.
我知道你们很害怕 因为我也很害怕
I know you're are scared, because I'm scared.
但那不是我们臣服于命运的借口
But that's no reason to accept our fate!
我们是Morty 我们的存在和Rick无关
We're Mortys! We're not defined by our relationships to Rick!
我们的命运由自己掌握
Our destiny is our own!
听起来好像本真Morty会说的话
This sounds like something the one true Morty might say.
我受够了做人肉护盾
I'm sick of being a human shield.
我想当一个园丁
I-I-I w- I want to be a gardener!
我想写真正疯狂刺激的动作小说
I want to write really crazy, intense action novels!
我不只是一个铁锤
I'm more than just a hammer!
他就是本真Morty
He is the one true Morty!
本真Morty
The one true Morty!
喂 老实点
Hey, keep it down!
你的人生真精彩呀 Rick
You've lived quite a life, Rick.
真可惜你看不到你的人生走向终结了
It's a real shame you're not gonna be around to see it through.
你在哭吗 为了一个Morty
You're crying? Over a Morty?
不 我只是对蠢货过敏
No, I'm just allergic to dipshits.
真可悲
Ugh. Pathetic.
我们都知道 如果世界上有什么真理
We both know that if there's any truth in the universe,
那就是Rick从来不会在意Morty
it's that Ricks don't care about Mortys.
尽管来吧 小混蛋
Do your worst, you little bastards!
杀了我啊 来啊 来啊
Kill me! Do it! Do it!
Morty 谢天谢地 把我弄出来
Morty! Thank god! Get me out of this.
快啊
Come on!
你真幸运 我不是Rick
You're lucky I'm not a Rick.
知道啦 没时间扯这些了
Point taken, but this is no time for arcs.
喂 你好
Yeah, hello.
嘿 我和O.J.有什么不同
Hey, what do me and O.J. not have in common?
{\an8\fs38}O.J.辛普森 著名的辛普森杀妻案
啊 你是谁
Huh? W-who is this?
不同点就在于 我找到真凶啦 贱人
I found the real killer, bitch!
快过来吧
Get over here!
喂 傻瓜 完事了 该走了
Yo, Ding-Dong, we're done here. Time to go.
哦 Jerry 我想该说再见了
Well, Jerry I guess this means goodbye.
啊 一定要走吗
W-w-well, does it have to?
我是说 你 你长得跟Rick一样
I mean, you, you look just like Rick.
说不定我们可以 除掉他
We could maybe, you know, get rid of him.
我可不是说一定要杀了他
I'm not saying kill him, necessarily.
我 我也不是说一定不能杀了他 但是
I, I'm also not saying necessarily not to kill him, but
Jerry 我们都知道 没用的
Jerry, w-we both know it wouldn't work.
是时候回归各自的生活了
It's time to go back to our lives.
我爱你 Jerry 我爱你
I love you Jerry, I love you.
这些Morty会怎么样
W-what, w-what's gonna happen to all these Mortys?
回家里 照常上学
They'll go back to their fimilies, attend school regularly,
玩电子游戏 交女朋友
play video games, date girls.
没了Rick的可怜小混蛋们
Poor little Rick-less bastards.
地球Rick C-137 委员会为其错误的指控道歉
Earth Rick C-137, the council apologizes for its false accusation,
作为对我们犯下的错误的弥补
and in the way of reparations for our terrible mistake,
我们将给予你这张票券作为补偿
we would like to compensate you with this voucher
用于免费换取一个替代的Morty
for a free replacement Morty in the event that
以防你当前的Morty...
your current Morty should...
你们能选个好点的时机吗
Uh, guys, not a good time.
Morty 我们走
Come on, Morty. Let's hit it.
现在能说了吧
Is it time for arcs yet, Rick?
我这个人肉隐形衣还是很厉害的
I did a pretty good job back there for a human cloaking device.
救了你一命
Saved your ass.
行了 Morty
All right, Morty.
少得意了 小心把逼吹破
Don't break an arm jerking yourself off.
真是难以置信 Rick
Man, I can't believe you, Rick.
刚才那么好的机会
That right there, that w- that was a great opportunity
你能稍微有点人性吗
to show a little humanity, you know?
和我稍微增进点感情
to connect with me a little.
你要想增进感情 去加入个什么傻逼俱乐部
Hey, Morty, you want connection, go be part of some stupid club,
就和那帮傻Rick一样
like all those dumb Ricks.
或许我不愿意真情流露
You know, maybe I don't connect
是因为我是最Rick的Rick
because I'm the Rick-est Rick there is.
所以 不用说
And, you know, it would g-go without saying
最Rick的Rick身边会有最Morty的Morty
that the rickest Rick would have the Morty-est Morty.
不用说 是吗
It would go without saying, huh?
当然了 你听见我说出来了吗
Yeah, it would. Did you hear me say it?
没
Nah.
最Morty的Morty
The Morty-est Morty.
不要太得意了 Bstuer Brown
Just don't get too big for your loafers, Buster Brown.
一个自大的Morty会导致很严重的后果
A cocky Morty can lead to some big problems.
对大家都没好处
It can be a real bad thing for everybody.
是吗 为什么
Oh, yeah? How's that?
你再大点我会跟你解释清楚的
U-uh, I'll explain when you're older.
真惨
What a mess.
{\an8\fs38}Buster Brown 漫画角色 一个特别淘气的小男孩
骄者必亡
Pride cometh before the fall.
他这算是罪有应得了吧
I guess he got what he deserved.
那是什么
What is that?
把激光除解器递给我
Hand me the laser defibulator.
我能来帮忙吗
Hey, guys, uh, c-can I help?
不 打扫厕所去
No! Go clean the toilets.
或不定有便便愿意和你交朋友
Maybe you'll make friends with some turds.
你让我们觉得做自己很惭愧
You make us ashamed to be ourselves.
天 我以前见过这种科技
My god. I've seen this technology before.
这个Rick被人远程遥控了
This Rick was being controlled remotely,
是别的什么人的傀儡
peppeteered by somebody else.
这是接收器
This is the receiver.
可是发射器在哪儿呢
Yeah, but where's the transmitter?
{\an8\fs38}Blonde Redhead 《For The Damaged Coda》
{\fs38}Wubba dubba dub dub\NWubba dubba dub dub!
嗨 Jerry
Oh. Hey, Jerry.
你在我房里干嘛呢
W-w-w-what are you doing in my room, buddy?
没什么 我只是来 检查下烟雾报警器
Nothing. I was just, um, checking the smoke detectors.
行吧 快出去
All right. Ok, get out.
那个傻逼在那儿干嘛
What's that dipshit doing out there?
你和他是朋友
Are you friends with him?
你知道他吃自己的屎的吧
You know he eats his own shit, right?
天啊 太有料了
Oh, my god, this is rich!
得有10个Rick我要打电话过去
I've got like 10 Ricks to call right now.

