
{\an8\fs32\fad(800,800)\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H666562&\b1}{\fn时尚中黑简体}翻译: 遥望 小萌 暑假中的Kimuu V僧
{\c&HFFFFFF&\b1\3c&H666562&}{\an8\fs32\fad(800,800)}{\fn时尚中黑简体}校对: 酱油薛
{\c&HFFFFFF&}{\an8\fs32\fad(800,800)\b1\3c&H666562&}{\fn时尚中黑简体}后期: 小萌
{\c&HFFFFFF&\an8}{\fs32\fad(800,800)\b1\3c&H666562&}{\fn时尚中黑简体\b1}压制: 凯撒
{\fs34}{\p1\c&H96955E&\fscx4200\fscy410\an8\fad(800,800)\pos(642,0)}m 0 0 b 0 0 0 0 0 0 b 0 0 0 0 0 0 b 0 4 0 9 0 13 b 4 13 9 13 13 13 b 13 9 13 4 13 0 {\p0}
{\pos(632,192)}{\fad(1000,0)}{\c&H00FEFEDB\t(0,2500,\c&H00D8D021)}瑞克与莫蒂
{\pos(617.333,622)}{\fad(500,0)}电波诚译
{\pos(617.333,666)}{\fad(500,0)}第一季 第十一集
{\fn方正喵呜体}{\fs70\c&H20F0FF&\b1}电波字幕组 欢迎您的加入\N{\fs34}\N{\fs65\b0}官方网站:www.dbfansub.com\N{\fs34}\N{\fs65\b0}新浪微博:@电波字幕组
- 再见老妈 再见老爸  - 开车小心
- Bye, mom! Bye, dad! - Drive carefully!
玩得开心哦 两位
Have fun, you two.
是 我们会努力寻找乐趣的 毕竟要去的是
Yes, we will have as much fun as possible on our...
泰坦尼克主题游
Titanic-Themed getaway.
麻烦你别闹脾气了
Let's lose the 'tude, please.
到时候肯定会非常浪漫的
It's supposed to be romantic.
说到灾难 爸 家里现在可归你管了
Speaking of disasters, dad, we are leaving you in charge, here.
知道啦 说完了吗
I know, c-can we wrap this up?
Morty和我在车库里弄的合成激光鳗鱼正在氧化呢
Morty and I have some synthetic laser eels oxidizing in the garage.
喂 好好听我说
Hey, don't blow me off.
我要定个规矩
I am drawing a line, okay?
要是我们回来发现房子和孩子有任何损伤
Any damage to this house or these children when we get back,
你就再也不能跟Morty去冒险了
and...n-no more adventures with Morty.
噢 天哪 Rick
Aw, geez, Rick.
要是我妈都这么说了 那肯定是认真的
If my mom's the one who's saying it, then you know it's pretty serious this time.
- 没错  - 没错
- That's right. - That's right.
等等 啥
Wait. What?
听着 作为看护者我可以承诺
Listen, you have my words as a caregiver,
一切都会没事的
everything's gonna be fine.
万一有事 那就听你的 不跟Morty去冒险了
And if not, like you say, no more adventures or whatever.
就像那首老歌唱的
It's like that old song
"Blop blop-a noop noop a-noop noop noop"{\fs38}\N"Blop blop-a noop noop a-noop noop noop."
你们不知道这首歌吗 Tiny Rogerts唱的
Y-you guys know that song? From Tiny Rogerts?
没听说过吗
You never heard of it?
就是 50年代的黑人娘炮
You know, the black effeminate guy from the '50s?
都不知道吗 唉 算了
No-nobody? A-all right, whatever.
管他的呢 快去你们那蠢旅游吧
Look, who cares? Just go on your stupid trip.
家里不准搞任何破坏
Not one thing out of place.
一处都不行
Not a single thing.
哇 既然已经踏上了不归路
Well, we're past the point of no return.
我要开个派对
I'm going to have a party.
我找到Jello了 你能把你妈的伏特加偷出来吗
I found Jello. Can you sneak your mom's vodka?
她当然有 我在你们家洗衣房里看到了
Yes, she does. I saw it in your laundry room.
听着 你们两个不能同时否认啊
Listen, you can't both be in denial about it.
好 再见
Okay bye.
Summer 不许你开派对
Summer, you can't throw a party!
记得老妈讲的吗
Remember what mom said?
是啊 要是事情搞砸了 你和外公Rick会受惩罚
Yeah, if anything gets messed up, you and grandpa Rick get punished.
而我嘛 只是个普通人 Morty
I'm only a human being, Morty.
Rick 快告诉Summer不许开派对
Rick, tell Summer she can't have a party!
Summer 你不能开派对
Uh, Summer, you can't have a party.
因为我要开派对 小妞
Because I'm having a party, bitch!
什么 Rick 不行
Oh, what?! Rick, you can't!
你说你要开派对是什么意思
What do you mean  you're having a party?
会有第三次元的鼻涕怪
Are some glip glops from the third dimension
跑过来打牌吗
going to come over and play cards or something?
"鼻涕怪" 你真走运 没让塔夫落基人听见
"Glip glop?" You're lucky a Trafilorkian doesn't hear you say that.
这是他们的敏感词吗
Is that like their N-word?
就好像敏感词和屏蔽词生了个娃
It's like the N-word and the C-word had a baby
然后被各种侮辱犹太人的词汇养大
and it was raised by all the bad words for jews.
听我说 我觉得我们三个可以
Listen, I think the three of us could just,
玩点简单的 比如出去逛逛街
have a nice time, like just hanging out, and, you know,
类似这种亲人间的互动
you know, doing a little bonding and...
去你的 这可是我和那些酷家伙
Screw that. This is my chance to
建立关系的机会
gain some footing with the cool kids.
这就是你开派对的目的
That's why you party?
孩子 你还真是花季少女啊
Boy, you really are 17.
那你为什么开派对
Why do you party?
当然是要嗨翻天啊 小屁孩
To get wriggedy wriggedy wrecked, son!
让你那些科幻朋友
Just keep your Sci-fi friends
离我的酷炫朋友远一点
away from my awesome ones.
好啊 你也让你的酷炫朋友
Yeah, and you keep your awesome friends
离我的小鱼面包远一点
away from my canapes.
晚餐过后 泰坦尼克2号 就会
After dinner, Titanic 2 will attach to
{\frx358\fry6\pos(236.6,197.4)\fs24\frz354.6}泰坦尼克
{\frx2\fry18\pos(235.2,307.6)\frz355.8\b1}享受浪漫{\b0}
{\frx0\fry10\pos(240,385.8)}经典重现
被轨道系统引导到我们的假冰山
the rail system near our replica iceberg,
然后这些管道里的液压
and the hydraulics encased in these tubes
会将整艘船沉入冰冷的海底
will execute a controlled sink into the icy depths.
这么经典的东西用这么老套的轨道系统
A rail system seems archaic for a attraction this impressive.
确定会沉吗
Are you sure the ship will sink?
我可以保证这船会沉的 它都沉了几千次了
I can assure you the ship will sink, as it has a thousand times before.
它是必沉无疑的
It is un-unsinkable.
看 这是去船头的队伍
Look, it's the line for bow!
Jerry 我好想回去边喝酒边看书
Jerry, I'd love to just kick back with a margarita and read.
不介意我跳过"我是世界之王"的桥段吧
Do you mind if I skip the whole "king of the world" bit?
这不是"我是世界之王"的桥段
Well, it's not the "king of the world" bit.
那是Jack和Fabrizio
That's Jack and Fabrizio.
这里是Rose对Jack说 "Jack 我在飞翔"桥段
This is where Rose says, "I'm flying Jack!"
随便吧 当独自来演戏的也没差
But whatever. I can be the only one to do it alone.
那 她怎么样
Well, what about her?
打扰一下 女士
Excuse me, ma'am.
你能否代替我一下
Would you like my place in line?
我 可能会有麻烦的
I, uh, I could get into trouble.
我们不会说出去的
We won't tell.
所以 你也是泰坦尼克迷吗
So... You're a Titanicfanatic?
恩 是的 我从刚开张就在这工作了
Oh, yes. I worked here since it opened,
但是我从来都没能参与进来
but I've never been able participate.
乐意效劳 Rose
Happy to help... Rose.
我超爱看多P群射的 不过
I love watching Bukkake. I mean, like,
我不知道自己情不情愿这么做
I don't know if I personally would ever do it...
- Brad 嘿  - 哟
- Brad! Hey! - Yo.
Brad来了
Brad is here!
快 把我头发弄得像喝醉了一样的
Quik, make my hair look drunk.
看哪 Tammy已经喝醉了 酷
Check it out. Tammy's already drunk. Cool.
信号灯亮了 谁需要救援
The beacon was activated. Who is in danger?
外公
Ugh! Grandpa!
鸟人
Birdperson!
很高兴没有紧急情况
I am pleased there is no emergency.
真有紧急情况 是操蛋的情况啦
Oh, there's an emergency, all right. A f**king emergency!
你上次打炮是什么时候啊 老哥
When's the last time you got laid, 'pers?
鸟人的交配季真是 不容易啊
It has been a... challenging mating season for Birdperson.
那今晚你可以鸟嘴湿润啦 客官
Then it's time to get your beak wet tonight, playah.
去找点乐子吧 鸟鸟鸟人
Go have some fun out there. Birdp-Bird-Birdperson.
天呐 你到底请了多少人啊 Rick
Oh, man, how many people did you invite, Rick?
人类吗 6个
Uh... people? Mm, six.
唷 你们好吗 鼻涕怪
Yo! What up, my glip glops?!
我靠
Oh, man!
你们知不知道家里是有垃圾桶的
Oh! Y-y-you know there's a garbage, right?
我靠 搞什么
Hey, uh, what the hell?
噢 这就是为什么不能邀请肉食怪和素食怪
Ooh. That's why you never invite a Floopy Poop and
参加同一个派对
a Shmoopy doop to the same party.
噢 噢 这太恶了
Oh, oh, g--oh, that's disgusting!
你们居然在我父母的床上搞
You guys are in my parents bed!
哦 对不起 我就是有点不舒服
Oh. Sorry. I'm not feeling too well.
想躺一会儿
I just needed to lie down for a bit.
哦 好 不好意思
Oh. Okay. Sorry.
天啊 这是在逗我吗
Oh, my god! Are you kidding me?!
大家都不了解齿轮战争的主要原因是
The thing people don't realize about the gear wars is
他们根部不了解齿轮
that it was never really about the gears at all.
哦 对 绝对的
Uh-huh. Yeah. No, no to-totally.
Rick 你要快点停止
Rick, you got to stop
Morty{\fs38}\NMorty!
你见过齿轮头吗
Have you met Gearhead?
嗨 你好
Hey, how's
Morty 他非常想听听关于齿轮产战争的事
Morty here, he he would love to hear all about the gear wars.
你对齿轮战争了解多少
How familiar are you with the gear wars, exactly?
呃 完全没头绪
Uh... not at all.
噢 太好了 我嫉妒你
Oh, boy. I envy you.
好的 这要从754年前说起
Okay, it was about 754 years ago.
噢 嗨 Morty
Oh, hey Morty!
给你介绍我的好朋友螃蟹人
Have you-- have you met my buddy Scropon?
又来了 Rick
Not again, Rick.
上个家伙陈词滥调的给我讲了20分钟
That last guy droned on for 20 minutes, you know?
于此同时整座房子快被摧毁了
And meanwhile, the whole house is being destroyed!
哇 Morty 这家伙的整个星球都被摧毁了
Whoa, Morty, this guy's entire planet was destroyed.
放尊重点
Have a little perspective.
嗨 Rick 真是个屎瓜派对啊 老兄
Hey, Rick, Squanchy  party, bro!
屎瓜奇
Aw! Squanchy!
这里有没有好地方让我屎瓜一下
Is there a good place for me to squanchar round here?
屎瓜奇 你可以随处屎瓜
Squanchy, you can squanch wherever you want, man.
米卡苏卡萨 老兄
Mi casa es su casa, dawg!
太好了
All right!
我喜欢你的屎瓜
I like your squanch!
Rick 屎瓜究竟是什么意思
Uh, Rick what exactly is "squanching"?
Morty 听着 在过去的一年中我们经理过这么多超酷的历险
Morty, listen we've had a lot of really cool adventures over the last year,
现在是时候放松一下了
but it's time to relax.
如果我现在放松的话 估计以后我们就没法历险了
Yeah, if I relax now, there might not even be any more adventures!
天哪 Morty 你愁死我了
Jesus, Morty, you're bumming me out.
在这几个小时内 咱们能不能假装什么事都没发生
Can't we just pretend like every thing's fine for a few hours,
然后好好享受一下 所有事以后再说
enjoy ourselves, and then worry about all this later?
你说的容易啊 Rick
Yeah, that's easy for you to say, Rick.
因为你什么都不在乎
You know, you like not caring about stuff.
可我怎么办
You know, wh-wh-what's in this for me?
别捣乱 慢动作孟巴斯
Knock it off, Slow Mobius!
哈哈 对不起 老兄 我就想秀一下我的超能力
Ha ha! sorry, dude! I'm just trying to show off my powers, bro!
不敢相信 她真的来了
I can't believe she's here.
那你还傻站着干嘛Morty
Well, what are you doing standing here, Morty?
去和他搭讪啊
Go. Talk to her.
今夜 你的目标就是壮大自己的男子气概
Tonight, the only adventure you're on is your cusping manhood.
噢 Rose
Oh, Rose. Whee!
这个 不会是我想的那个吧
Is that what I think it is?
嗯 每对情侣都有机会重演Jack在海上淹死的桥段
Yes, every couple gets to re-create Jack's drowning at the end of the movie.
太浪漫了
It's so romantic.
我等不及和Beth一起经历
I can't wait to do that with beth.
我不明白 Jerry
I don't know, Jerry.
恕我直接 你老婆看起似不怎么感兴趣
With all due respect, it seems like your wife may not be that interested.
快看
Look!
前方有冰山
Iceberg, right ahead!
自助餐现已关闭
The buffet is now closed.
前方有冰山 自助餐现已关闭
Iceberg, right ahead! The buffet is now closed.
长官
Uh, sir?
没有出现故障
There's not a problem.
什么叫没有出现故障
What do you mean there's not a problem?
制导系统没有把我们带入碰撞航线
The guidance system isn't putting us on a direct collision course.
船就要错过冰山了
This ship is about to completely miss the giant iceberg!
快想办法
Well, do something!
转舵 撞上去
Steer into it!
我尽力
I'm trying!
太迟了
It's too late.
女士们 先生们
Ladies and gentlemen...
不要振作起来
Don't brace yourselves.
不 不 搞什么啊
No! No! What happened?!
他们的制导系统坏了
Their rail system must have failed.
我的天啊 我们沉不了了
Oh, my god! we're not gonna sink!
今晚一定要搞个女的
Totally gonna get laid tonight.
我喜欢你的羽毛
I like your feathers.
它们就是为了吸引异性
They are designed to attract the attention of the female.
看来起作用了
It's working.
Tammy 我应该告诉你
Tammy, I should let you know
我刚与我的灵魂配偶结束了一段密切的结合
I just got out of a highly intense soul bond with my previous spirit mate.
我不需要灵魂结合
I'm not looking to get into a soul bond.
我需要的是
I'm just looking for...
相信这个我能做到
I believe birdperson can arrange that.
Summer 好久没见你上长笛练习课了
Hey, Summer, haven't seen you at flute practice in a while.
Summer 别告诉我你认识她
Summer, don't tell me you're friends with her.
你开什么玩笑
Are you kidding me?
我都不知道她来干嘛
I don't even know what she's doing here.
这不行 Summer 这是个派对
Whoa. Not cool, Summer. This is a party.
所有人都应该被受欢迎
Everybody should be welcome.
麻烦了 是谁邀请的阿道夫·林肯勒?
Oh, great. Who invited Abradolph Lincoler?
不是所有人都应该被受欢迎的吗
I thought everyone was welcome.
这不一样
It's not the same Summer.
林肯勒是个疯子
Lincoler is a crazed maniac
他是由阿道夫希特勒和亚布拉罕林肯的基因混合创造出来的
just a misguided effort of mine to create a morally neutral super leader
{\an8\fs38\pos(638.857,42.286)}奥地利裔德国政治人物，纳粹党党魁，1934年至1945年为德国元首.
{\an8\fs38\pos(638.857,0)}Adolf Hitler 阿道夫·希特勒
{\an8\fs38\pos(643.429,81.143)}Abraham Lincoln 亚伯拉罕·林肯 美国政治家、思想家。第16任美国总统，颁布了《宅地法》、《解放黑人奴隶宣言》
道德中立的超级领袖
by combing the DNA of Adolf Hitler and Abraham Lincoln.
但结果却是一个差劲 神经的失败者
Turns out it just adds up to a lame, weird loser.
Rick 你把我带到这世上 让我看到了这个苦难 罪恶的
Rick, you brought me into this world, a suffering abomination tortured
二次元世界
by the duality of its being.
或许我应该在你生命流逝中看到世界的和平
But I shall finally know peace when I watch the life drain from your wretched body!
靠 你干什么 老兄
Whoa. What's up, man?
和你没关系 娃
I have no quarrel with you, boy.
"娃" 你什么意思
"Boy"? What's that supposed to mean?
只是 听着 我不是有意的  只是
It's just... look, I-I don't know how you thought I meant it, but...
别看我 老哥
Don't look at me, dude.
你瞧 我有一半是亚伯拉罕·林肯 所以
Look, I'm half-Abraham Lincoln, so
所以我应该跪在你面前 拍你马屁吗
So I should get on my knees and kiss your ass?!
这 不是 但是 那个...
Well, no, but... you know?
那个什么
What do I know?
第三帝国将会统治一千年
That the third Reich will reign for a thousand years?
{\an8\fs38} 纳粹德国有两个官方国名
{\an8\fs38}分别为1933年至1939年使用的第三帝国和1939年至1945年的大德意志帝国.
别烦他 Brad
Leave him alone, Brad.
闪一边去 Jessica
Stay out of this, Jessica!
打他 Brad 打他 打他
Kick his ass, Brad! Kick his ass!
打他 打他
Kick his ass! Kick his ass!
Brad{\fs38}\NBrad!
蠢货
Stupid!
Rick{\fs38}\NRick!
我这是在帮你Morty
I just did you a favor, Morty.
不好意思让你看到了刚刚的局面
Sorry about all that.
Rick的狐朋狗友可多了
Rick has some really strange friends.
Brad简直就是个混球
Brad is such a jerk.
整天想着该如何逞男人
He's always tyring to prove what a man he is.
我只想找个温柔体贴的男朋友罢了
I just want to find somebody nice and sweet.
Jessica 我带你去看些东西吧
Jessica, can I show you something?
哇 瞧瞧这里的东西
Wow, look at all this stuff.
是啊 这里可是我和外公Rick的科学工作室
Yeah. This is me and my Granda Rick's sci-fi workshop.
看看这个
Check this out.
好漂亮哦
It's beautiful.
其实嘛 Jessica
You know, Jessica.
我有些想和你说却一直没说出口的话
There's something I've always wanted to tell you.
那是什么啊 Morty
What's that, Morty?
- 我觉得你是世界上  - 不 那个
- I think that you're the most... - No, that...
衣柜里好像传出了奇怪的声音
Those weird sounds coming from the closet over there.
- 我的天哪  - 喂 我在这里屎瓜呢
- Oh My God. - Hey, I'm squanching in here.
天哪 真是恶心透了
Oh my god, that is so disgusting.
好痛 哦 啊 完了
Ow... oh, oh, crap.
天上有硕大的行星
Big star in the sky.
供氧不成问题的大气层
Oxygen-rich atmosphere.
巨型的睾状怪物
Giant testicle monsters.
这里没问题 我们继续狂欢吧
We'll be fine. Let's party.
我对天发誓 Morty
I swear to god, Morty.
要不是里面那群人还在狂欢
If it weren't for the fact that everyone's still having a blast in there,
我现在肯定在对你发火
I would be so furious with you right now.
听到了没 Morty
Oh, man. You hear that, Morty.
你可真把Summer惹毛了
You really lucked out with Summer on that one.
你们是怎么保持淡定的
How are you guys not freaking out right now?
整栋屋子现在可都在异次元
The whole house is sitting in another dimension.
我们该怎么办啊
I mean, what the hell are we supposed to do?
爸妈回来 会秒杀我们的
Mom and dad are gonna kill us.
- 我要疯掉了啊 Rick  - 冷静 Morty 冷静
- I'm losing it here, Rick. - Relax, Morty, relax.
没事的
It's gonna be fine.
我们只要出去找些凯拉辛结晶回来就行了
All we have to do is go out and find us some Kalaxian Crystals.
我操
Shit, mother f**kers.
Morty 这里以南几英里的地方就有凯拉辛结晶了
Kalaxian Crystals, Morty, just a few miles south of here.
行 我们出发吧
Ok, let's go then.
我们必须现在去找结晶 Rick
We got to go get those crystals right now, Rick.
等 等 等 Morty 我不能和你去
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Morty, I can't go with you.
我得呆在这里 保证这里一切安好
I got to hang back and make sure everything stays cool here, you know.
我是说 万一有人不下心摔碎了什么的
I mean, who knows what... what if somebody breaks something?
我也是 得留下来
Yeah, me too. I should stay.
你们谁有阿司匹林吗
You guys have any Aspirin?
Morty 太好了
Oh, hey, Morty. This is perfect.
你可以带着林肯勒一起去
You can take Lincoler with you.
拜托 我现在哪里也不去 没看见我受伤了吗
Hey man, I'm not going anywhere. I'm injured.
闭嘴 林肯勒
Shut up, Lincoler.
这是作为损毁客厅的补偿
It's the least you can do for wrecking the living room.
对哦 Nancy 你也应该去的
Yeah, and Nancy, you should go too.
什么 为什么是我
What? Why... why me?
因为 因为你 很会吹笛子嘛
Because... you... you're so good at playing the flute.
不好意思给大家带来了不便
Sorry for the inconvenience folks.
{\fs24\frx358\fry8\frz5.54\pos(488,384)}泰坦尼克{\fs22}
我们应该很快就能进行沉船了
We should resume sinking shortly.
与此同时 请待在船上
In the mean time, please stay on the ship
{\fs36\frx358\fry14\pos(355.429,172.572)\frz356.8}客户服务
并享受这免费赠送的卡梅隆洋葱圈
and enjoy a complimentary plate of James Cameronion Rings.
真是太好了 船不沉就算了
Great. Not only the ship not sinking,
还被剧透了
but now the fourth wall has been broken.
我要回房 去看完那本小说了
I am gonna go back to the room and finish my book.
你应该去找那个叫Lucy的女人
You should find that Lucy woman.
但 但是
But...but...
那个 Jerry 我带你去看些东西吧
You see, Jerry. May I show you something?
如果一切按照计划行驶
Had everything gone as planned,
这整片区域都会被淹没
this entire area would be underwater.
我挺想看到那场景的
I would have liked to see it.
真是一场"泰坦尼克"悲剧啊 懂吗
This trip has been a "Titanic" faliure. Get it?
- 哦哦哦  - 抱我 Jerry
- Ooh. - Draw me, Jerry.
天哪 那个 Lucy 啊
Oh... boy... Lucy, wow...
这 和我想象的不太一样
Uh... This isn't what I had in mind.
但是时刻总算到来了
But it's the perfect moment.
我们梦寐了16年的场景啊
We've been dreaming about this for 16 years.
那个 不是像现在这样的 也不是和你
Um... Not like this... Not...not with you.
- 你会抱我的  - 啊啊啊
- You are gonna draw me. - Aah.
然后你要在那辆车里干我
Then you're going to f**k me in that car over there.
说来也奇怪 我觉得所有男人都生来是平等的
It's weird, cause I definitely think that all men are created equal.
- 但是 与此同时又  - 行了
- But, at the same time... - Okay...
结晶应该就在这里附近了
Um... the crystals should be really close.
在那里
There they are.
等等 这里不太对劲
Wait. Something's not right.
快拿结晶
Get the crystals.
野兽交给我处理就好
I'll handle the beast.
准备从你那可悲的基因里解脱吧
Prepare to be emancipated from your own inferior genes.
Summer会重新喜欢上我的
Summer's gonna like me again.
林肯勒 快 我们快离开这里吧
Lincoler, come on. Let's get out of here.
我的旅程结束了 Morty
My journey is over, Morty.
我有件重要的事要告诉你
I have something important to tell you.
*我的齿轮 旋转了千年*
*And the gears, they tuned for a thousand years*
*直到末日才终结*
*Until the dark day that they stopped*
Rick 我拿到了 我拿到结晶了
Rick, I got them. I got the crystals.
太好了 Morty
Alright, you did it, Morty.
Rick 等等
Rick, wait.
你得知道件事情
There's something you need to know.
不是林肯勒 我们是绝对拿不到结晶的
I couldn't have done it without Lincoler.
他说他很抱歉
He said that he was really sorry
然后 他一直像爱爸爸那样爱着你
and that he loves you like a father.
他只是想被你接受
He only wanted you to accept him
他希望自己所做的最后一点一滴能挽回他在你心中的印象
and he hopes that his final act would redeem him in your eyes.
他牺牲了自己来拯救大家 Rick
He sacrificed himself to save all of us, Rick.
他死了
He died.
至少他没有白白牺牲
Well, at least he didn't die in vain.
他拿到了结晶
He got these crystals.
而这些宝贝们来拯救这无聊至极的派对了
And these babies just saved this lame-ass party.
Wubba lubba dub dub{\fs38}\NWubba lubba dub dub.
放点什么啦 快点 放点音乐
Play something. Somebody, play something.
等等 你说什么
Wait a minute, what?
*右脚往前踩 左脚往后踏*
*Put your right foot forward and your left foot back*
*像诺迪克跑步机 两边走动*
*Then slide around like a NordicTrack*
*往左*
*Move to the left*
*往右*
*Step to the right*
*抖抖胳膊 看看灯*
*Wiggle your elbows, and look up into the light*
*这就是 这就是 这就是Rick舞*
*It's the, it's the, it's the Rick Dance*
*这就是 这就是 这就是Rick舞*
*It's the, it's the, it's the Rick Dance*
慢动作孟巴斯 来一束时间光波
Slow Mobius, hit me with the clock beam.
*这就是 这就是 这就是Rick舞*
*It's the, it's the, it's the Rick Dance*
这就是Rick舞
That's the Rick dance. Alright.
刚刚那是个啥
What the hell was that?
我以为找结晶是为了让我们回家
I thought those crystals were supposed to help us get home or something.
什么 不 不 不 我随时都能把我们送回去
What? No, no, no... I can get us home whenever I want to.
对了 说起那些结晶
But, listen. Speaking of those crystals,
其余能给我吗
can I get the rest of them?
我渐渐回来了 Morty
I'm starting to come down, Morty.
凯拉辛结晶效果强劲就是时效太短
Crystal Kalaxian is a strong but fleeting high.
我就是这么看这结晶的 Rick
That's what I think of your crystals, Rick.
Morty 你个蠢货
Oh, Morty. You idiot.
还有谁有K-辛么
Does anybody else have any more K-Lax?
鸟人 屎瓜
Birdperson? Squanchy?
不要屎瓜我啦
Don't squanch at me.
好了 大伙 派对正式结束
Alright, everybody. Party is officially over.
Rick 现在立刻把我们带回家
Rick, take us home now.
行啦 行啦 行啦 Morty 你个派对老鼠屎
Alright, alright. Fine, Morty, you party pooper buzzkill.
- Morty 你太可恶了  - 管你叫什么名字的 你最烂了
- Boo, boo. Morty sucks. - Boo. You suck whatever your name is.
烂透了 Morty 你烂到爆了
Boo. Morty, you're the worst, Morty.
齿轮才刚刚开始转呢
But these gears just started turning.
快画完了吗 Jerry
Almost finished, Jerry?
呃 快了
Uh, almost.
我还没有完全捕捉到你美丽双眸的神韵
I haven't quite captured your beautiful eyes.
肯定也差不多了 快过来
I'm sure it's good enough,move!
每个周末都有几对Jack和Rose在这辆车上度过他们的泰坦尼克浪漫之旅
Every weekend Jacks and Roses have their Titanic experience in this car,
而我负责事后清理
and I have to mop it up.
这厢板掉下来能让清理容易点
The floor drops out to make it easier.
现在轮到我在车里翻云覆雨了
But now it's my turn.
我们将会达到快乐的巅峰 把车里搞得雾气腾腾
We're going to get it， nice and steamy in there,
我要在有蒸汽的玻璃上留下一个大手印
And I'm going to slam my hand on the steam and leave a nice handprint.
然后你要进入我的身体 好好爱惜我
And then you're going to love inside of me.
不能弄得一团糟 事后也不能清理
No mess, no clean.
Beth{\fs38}\NBeth!
你看到我认为亚马逊电纸书不好使一定很高兴吧
Bet you're glad I think kindles are dumb now.
我忍不住地觉得挺愧疚的
I can't help but feel a little guilty.
我没把Lucy往强奸犯那方面想
I didn't peg Lucy for a rapist.
那强奸犯应该长什么样子 Beth
What does a rapist look like exactly, Beth?
应该是一个穿着牛仔外套
Is it a Slavic man wearing a denim jacket
留着稀拉胡子 一嘴水泡还有廉价香槟味
With a patchy beard and the scent of cheap champagne
斯拉夫男人吗
waft over his blister-pocked lips?
你在说什么
What?
行啦 至少你免费得到了些东西
Well, at least you got all these free stuff.
应该够满足你的泰坦尼克瘾一阵子的了
Should be enough to satisfy your Titanic Jones for a while.
我坐不下了
I'm not going to fit.
Beth 听我说
Beth,listen to me.
你会成功离开这里的
You're going to get out of here.
你会继续你的生活 然后
You're gonna go on,and...
Jerry 把那块门板扔了吧
Jerry, just leave the door.
这不是门板 Beth 这是残骸
It's not a door, Beth. It's debris.
我不管 快扔了它
I don't care, just leave it.
好吧
Yeah,okay.
是海角惊魂耶
"Cape Fear"! "Cape Fear"!
{\an8\fs38}《海角惊魂》 1962电影 讲述一名刚出狱的强奸犯怪罪于导致他入狱的律师，对他复仇的故事
我在复原海角惊魂里的场景耶
I'm I'm doing I'm I'm going to do like from "Cape Fear"!
屎瓜们
Hey, squanchers!
派对在我家继续屎瓜着
The party's squanching on at my place!
太好了 我也要去
Cool, I'm coming too.
哦 不 对于一个屎瓜派对来说你不够屎瓜
Uh, no. You're not squanchy enough for a squanchy party.
什么
What?
Nancy告诉了我们你有多贱
Nancy told us what a bitch you are.
各位 说真的 Nancy
Guys, seriously. Nancy?
Summer 你为人太差
Summer, you're a bad person.
你只想着让受欢迎的人喜欢你
All you care about is having popular people like you.
这可不是阿道夫·林肯勒主张的
That's not what Abradolph Lincoler stood for.
好吧 搞清楚他的主张不容易
Well, it was hard to pin down what he stood for,
但是他肯定不是为这个而死的
But it's certainly not what he died for.
下次我再开派对
Next time I party
我就只管让自己兴奋得精疲力尽就好
I'm just gonna focus on getting totally wrecked.
你太明智了
You're so wise.
我帮你一起收拾好吗
May I assist you with that?
当然好 谢谢
Uh, sure, yeah, thanks.
Morty 你知道"Wubba lubba dub dub"什么意思吗
Morty, do you know what "Wubba lubba dub dub" means?
那只是Rick愚蠢又没有逻辑的口头禅而已
Uh, that's just Rick's stupid nonsense catchphrase.
这并不是没有逻辑的
It's not nonsense at all.
在我们那里
In my people's tongue,
这句话的意思是"我很痛苦 请帮帮我"
It means "I am in great pain,please help me"
那我告诉你吧 他说的意思正好相反
Well, I got news of you, he's saying it ironically.
不 Morty
No, Morty.
你的外公确实非常痛苦
Your grandfather is, indeed, in very deep pain.
这就是他不得不麻痹自己的原因
That is why he must numb himself.
- 得了吧 呃  - 我叫鸟人
- Come on,uh... - Birdperson
得了吧 鸟人
Come on ,Birdperson.
Rick没有那么复杂
Rick's not that complicated.
他只是一个大混蛋而已
He's just a huge asshole.
那为什么你还这么在乎以后能不能和他
Then why do you care so much if you are no longer allowed to
继续探险之旅
continue on your adventures together?
看起来命运给了能让你永远远离Rick
It appears fate has presented you with an opportunity
获得自由的机会啊
to free yourself of Rick forever.
你知道吗 你说对了
You know what? You're right.
我根本不应该担心
I shouldn't even care.
这也许是对我最有利的事了
This is probably the best thing that could have happened to me.
我已经厌烦和Rick一起探险了
I'm sick of having adventures with Rick.
我们那儿还有一句谚语"Gubba nub nub doo rahkah"
My people have another saying "Gubba nub nub doo rahkah."
意思是"只要这事能让你安心入睡 就去做吧"
It means "whatever lets you sleep at night."
嘿 爸妈已经快到家了
Guys, mom and dad are, like, right around the corner.
这是你抉择的时刻 Morty
This is your moment, Morty.
明智地选择吧
Choose wisely.
Tammy{\fs38}\NTammy!
天啊 我们完蛋了
Wow, we are so screwed.
Rick 醒一醒
Rick, wake up!
等下 等下 停
Wait, wait, wait, stop.
Rick 你得赶快做点什么
Rick, you got to do something quick!
我爸妈快到家了
My parents are home.
好 好的 等 等会儿
Uh, all all right, all right. Hold hold on.
真解渴
Ah, so good.
我的天啊 他们上车道了
Oh,my god. They're walking up the driveway.
把那个东西拿给我
Bring me the thing.
啊 什么东西
What what thing?
那个东西 就是那个
The thing, the thing, the...
上面有按钮和灯的那个 还能响的东西
It's got, like, buttons on it and lights on it. It beeps.
Rick 车库里所有东西都长这样
Rick, that describes everything in your garage!
你是说这个吗
Do you mean this?
Summer拿 拿对了
Summer for for the win!
好了 现在就行了
All right, that should do it.
你干了什么
Whoa! What did you do?
你自己看
Uh, see for yourself.
哇
Whoa!
没错 所有东西都跟着时间一起被冻结了
Yeah, everything's frozen in time.
慢动作孟巴斯还以为只有他会这个呢
Yeah,and Slow Mobius thinks he's all that.
能静止多久
For how long?
不知道 你们想持续多久
I don't know. How long do you guys want?
一个星期 一个月
A week? A month?
我们能先打扫屋子再决定吗
Can we start cleaning the house and see how we feel?
- 史上最大烂片  - 我没话说了
- Worst movie ever. - Dumb.
哦 真是浪费时间
Ooh, what a waste of time.
听懂了吗 因为现在时间冻结了
Get it? You know, 'cause it's forzen?
这真是有趣啊
This has been so much fun.
嘿 Rick 这么长时间
Hey, Rick, you know this whole time,
我都没听你说过你以前老说的"Wubba lubba dub dub"了
I haven't once heard you say that "Wubba lubba dub dub" thing that you usually say.
因为我不需要说了 我已经有了新的口头禅
Don't need to, I have a new catchphrase.
是吗 是什么 Rick
Oh, yeah?  What's that, Rick?
我爱我的外孙和外孙女
I love my grandkids.
骗到你们啦 开玩笑的 我的新口头禅是
Psych! Just kidding, my new catchphrase is,
"我他妈才不在乎"
"I don't give a f**k".
{\an8\fs38}BGM: Booty Bass - Shake That Ass Bitch
播演职员表吧
Roll credits!
播演职员表 开始
Roll the credits, go!
第一季结束啦
That's the end of season 1!
混蛋们 第一季终结啦
That's the end motherf**ker!
"我他妈才不在乎"是我的新口头禅
"I don't give a f**k" is my new catchphrase!
去你妈的
F**k you!
这就是第一季全部内容 耶
That's season 1, boom!
第一季已经甩在你们面前啦混蛋们
Season 1 in your face, motherf**ker!
我要复仇
Revenge!
派对
Party!
天哪 拜托停下来
Oh, please, stop!
嘿 兄弟
Hey, brah!
我搞不懂了
I don't understand.
你很享受这样吗 你喜欢这样吗
Are you enjoying this? Do you like this?
当然 你懂的 老兄
Yeah,you know it, dawg!

